good morning my name is Matt Stein and
早上好，我叫马特·斯坦，
I'm a part of the platform engineering
我是平台工程的一部分
team with cloud foundry at pivotal and
与Cloud Foundry团队合作
we do lots of very interesting things
我们做了很多非常有趣的事情
one of those is helping our customers to
其中之一是帮助我们的客户
understand what it takes to start to
了解开始需要什么
operate in this new world of cloud and
在这个新的云世界中运营，
continuous delivery DevOps and and a lot
持续交付DevOps等等
of the other ideas that are sort of
其他一些想法
floating around in this space right now
现在在这个空间中漂浮
and one of them that you may have heard
还有你可能听说过的其中之一
of is this architectural style known as
这种建筑风格被称为
micro services and so both continuous
微服务等都是连续的
delivery in microcircuits are going to
在微电路中的交付将
be the focus of the talk and within the
成为谈话的焦点，并在
context of a couple of things first of
首先是两件事的背景
all pivotal CF which is a littles
所有关键的CF都是一点
commercial distribution of cloud foundry
云铸造的商业分销
and spring cloud which is a newly
还有 Spring 的云
announced set of projects that we first
我们首先宣布了一系列项目
unveiled at Spring one this year and so
于今年 Spring 一期揭幕
I'll be talking to you a little bit
我会跟你说一点
about how those two products dovetail to
关于这两种产品如何与
to make this whole architectural style a
使整个建筑风格
lot easier to to develop and also to
更容易开发，而且
manage as you run it in production
在生产中运行时进行管理
setting but first of all I just want to
设置，但首先我只想
kind of level set things a little bit
有点水平设置的东西
and for whatever reason I'm having
不管出于什么原因
trouble advancing my slides there we'll
麻烦推进我的幻灯片，我们将
go that route so let's talk about
走那条路，让我们来谈谈
continuous delivery and basically what I
持续交付，基本上我
want to do is boil that down to a very
想要做的是将其煮沸
basic concept what are we trying to do
基本概念我们要做什么
we're trying to shorten the length of
我们正在尝试缩短
time from someone in our business having
与我们业务中某人的时间
an idea that we think is actually going
我们认为实际上正在发展的想法
to be profitable for us to that idea
使我们对这个想法有利可图
actually delivering on that profit we
实际兑现我们的利润
all know there are many different
都知道有很多不同
activities that we have to accomplish
我们必须完成的活动
between those two points in time and so
在这两个时间点之间等等
idea is just to match those things
想法只是为了匹配那些东西
together as much as possible there's a
尽可能在一起
lot of different ways that we do that
我们这样做的许多不同方式
one of the first ways that we do that is
我们这样做的第一种方法是
we look at all the things that we're
我们看所有的东西
doing right now that are
现在正在做的是
actually delivering value along that
真正实现价值
line and we start to try to eliminate
线，我们开始尝试消除
those from our process but the next
那些来自我们的过程，但下一个
thing that we do is we look at what are
我们要做的是看看
those activities that we have to engage
我们必须从事的那些活动
in but that could be automated that we
在，但可以自动化，我们
could have computers doing on our behalf
可以让计算机代表我们做
so that human beings can focus on sort
让人类可以专注于排序
of the creative innovative tasks that
创造性的创新任务
only we are capable of and the real
只有我们有能力和真正的
question is okay that sounds great and
问题很好，听起来不错，
how do I actually do that practically
我实际上该如何做
and there are a lot of different
而且有很多不同
approaches to that and you know one of
方法，你知道其中之一
the places that many of us start as we
我们很多人开始的地方
go we read a lot of books and we try to
去，我们读了很多书，我们试图
figure out how can we get there but I
弄清楚我们如何到达那里，但我
don't want you to have to go down that
不想你不得不拒绝
road I just want you to kind of boil
我只想让你煮沸
this down to really a basic idea that
这归结为一个基本的想法
what we're used to doing is we're used
我们已经习惯了
to building something and then deploying
建立东西然后部署
that something and all I want to do is
我要做的就是
flip those tasks around instead of
翻转这些任务而不是
building something and then deploying
建立一些东西然后部署
something I wanted to avoid something
我想避免的事情
and then build something that sounds
然后建立听起来的东西
kind of weird at face value but
面值有点奇怪，但
basically the idea is all of the work
基本上，这就是所有工作
that I would normally have to do to get
我通常必须要做的是
me from I've demoed to the customer and
我从我降级到客户和
they liked the product that we've built
他们喜欢我们制造的产品
too that is actually running in a
也实际上是在
production environment and real users
生产环境和真实用户
are using it all of that work I want to
正在使用我想要的所有工作
front-load that in my development
在我的开发工作中担当重任
process and to do that I'm going to need
过程和要做的，我将需要
to probably build some very basic
建立一些非常基本的
skeleton of something that I can deploy
我可以部署的东西的骨架
and we'll see if spring boot makes it
我们会看看 spring boot 是否成功
incredibly simple to have a very basic
非常简单，拥有非常基本的
deployable web app that actually does a
实际执行
very few interesting things without me
没有我，很少有有趣的事情
actually writing any lines of production
实际写任何生产线
code so we're already enabled by spring
代码，因此我们已经在 Spring 启用
to get to that point very quickly and so
很快达到这一点
we take that and then we build our
我们接受这一点，然后我们建立我们的
deployment pipeline we build our testing
部署管道，我们建立测试
pipeline and then we start to hang
管道，然后我们开始挂起
features on that scale and as soon as we
规模如此之大，而我们
hang a feature on that skeleton we say
在我们说的骨架上挂一个功能
can we go to production with it well the
我们可以很好地进行生产吗
answer is yes
答案是肯定的
because we've done all the work so now
因为我们已经完成了所有工作
it just becomes a business choice you
它只是成为您的业务选择
know does the business want to actually
知道企业实际上想要
deploy that thing that we've built the
部署我们已经建立的东西
production and when we do that we can
生产，当我们这样做时，我们可以
actually move much more quickly which is
实际上移动得更快
ultimately our goal and there are
最终我们的目标是
businesses doing this so the one that I
企业这样做，所以我
like to highlight very often is Warner
经常要强调的是华纳
Music Warner Music at about 45 years of
音乐华纳音乐已有45年历史了
IT legacy in their business and that
他们的业务中的IT遗产
legacy was causing them to suffer
遗产使他们受苦
six-month delivery times for very basic
最基本的六个月交货时间
services that they wanted to deliver and
他们想要提供的服务以及
so what they decided to do was they took
所以他们决定要做的是
open source cloud flowing under Condry
Condry下的开源云
they took spring they took some data
他们拿了 Spring 他们拿了一些数据
stores like Cassandra and they built a
像卡桑德拉（Cassandra）这样的商店，他们建立了一个
new what they called software factory
他们称之为软件工厂的新工厂
platform that went through and
经过的平台
accomplished all of the tasks that I've
完成了我已经完成的所有任务
already talked about and when they did
已经谈论过，什么时候做的
that they were actually able to shorten
他们实际上能够缩短
their delivery time from 6 months with a
他们的交货时间从6个月开始，
team of 10 to 6 weeks with a team of 10
10至6周的团队，每组10个人
for roughly equivalent services and
大致相等的服务
basically what that boiled down to was
基本上归结为
they were able to keep this iterative
他们能够保持这种迭代
wheel spinning this idea that we never
滚转这个想法，我们从来没有
know when we're actually done and in
知道我们什么时候实际完成
fact if we're building a true product we
事实上，如果我们要制造出真正的产品，我们
never are actually done until we don't
直到我们不做，才真正完成
need the capability delivered by that
需要那个提供的能力
product anymore so what we want to do is
产品了，所以我们要做的是
enable ourselves to keep getting
使我们不断获得
feedback keep responding to that
反馈不断回应
feedback and keep delivering a better
反馈并不断提供更好的
product as that wheel spins and that may
车轮旋转的产品
be the result of direct customer
是直接客户的结果
conversation or as you see in this outer
对话或您在外部看到的
arrow here increasingly more this idea
箭头在这里越来越多的这个想法
of we're capturing events that are
我们正在捕获的事件是
happening in the code and streaming
发生在代码和流中
those of analytics that we can study and
我们可以学习的分析
make decisions on and ultimately pour
做出决定并最终倾泻
back into the application and have
回到应用程序并拥有
real-time behavioural changes based on
实时行为变化基于
what our users are doing so there are a
我们的用户正在做什么，所以有一个
few other aspects that are sort of
其他一些方面
forcing us in different directions
迫使我们朝着不同的方向前进
beyond
超越
just this idea of continuous delivery
只是这种持续交付的想法
and iteration there's also this idea
迭代也有这个想法
were wanting to operate at increasingly
想要以越来越高的速度运转
higher scale and we figured out several
更高的规模，我们找出了几个
years ago actually that vertical scaling
年前实际上是垂直扩展
was simply too slow and too expensive
太慢了，太贵了
for us to accomplish our goals if we
如果我们能够实现目标
have to go requisition new hardware in
必须去购买新硬件
order to get more processing power so
为了获得更多的处理能力，所以
that we can serve the load to the users
我们可以为用户提供负载
that we have we just can't move back
我们拥有我们只是无法后退
enough and then as that demand
足够，然后根据需求
fluctuates it's not like we can throw
波动不像我们可以扔
away hardware that we bought very easily
我们很容易购买的硬件
it's just not something it works very
这不是一个很有效的东西
well so we move towards virtualization
好，所以我们朝着虚拟化迈进
we move towards obtaining infrastructure
我们走向获得基础设施
through api's with infrastructure as a
通过api与基础架构
service so using things like AWS and
服务，例如使用AWS和
Google Cloud and others and then now we
Google Cloud等，然后我们
have this next evolution into deploying
进行部署的下一步发展
things with containers so I'm sure many
容器的东西，所以我敢肯定
of you have heard of projects like
你们当中有人听说过类似的项目
docker that attempt to allow us to
试图允许我们
acquire multiple instances of
获取多个实例
applications even more quickly because
应用程序更快，因为
instead of spinning up hold the machines
而不是把机器拉起来
we're actually spinning up just
我们实际上只是在旋转
containers inside of larger machines and
大型机器内部的容器和
so we've gone through the spectrum of it
所以我们经历了它的范围
takes weeks 2 days 2 min hours 2 minutes
需时2周2天2小时2分钟
2 now seconds or even sub seconds to be
现在是2秒，甚至不到几秒
able to deploy new instances of apps so
能够部署新的应用程序实例，因此
that's another thing driving us towards
那是促使我们走向的另一件事
new architectural directions and finally
新的建筑方向，最后
this idea that we can no longer afford
我们再也负担不起的想法
to pretend that the user sitting at a
假装用户坐在
workstation using a computer that's
工作站使用的计算机
tethered to a desk is our primary
拴在桌子上是我们的首要任务
customer in the US we measured the
美国的客户，我们对
traffic on the Internet
互联网流量
this year and in January was the first
今年和一月是第一个
time that we found that now the majority
我们发现大多数人的时间
of Internet traffic in the United States
美国的互联网流量
is coming from mobile devices so not
来自移动设备，所以不是
someone sitting at a computer but
有人坐在电脑前
someone on the road whether it's a phone
路上有人是手机
or a tablet
或平板电脑
or some other more mobile device whether
还是其他移动设备
it's Apple Android Windows Phone
这是Apple Android Windows Phone
whatever it may be the vast majority of
不管是绝大多数
our users are now interacting with this
我们的用户正在与此互动
at more amounts of time for more
在更多的时间更多
locations and quite literally just more
位置，实际上只是更多
people or interacting with our services
人或与我们的服务互动
than ever before and so we're starting
比以往任何时候，所以我们开始
to operate at differing levels of scale
以不同的规模运作
and also different levels of acceptable
以及不同程度的可接受
response time than we have in the past
响应时间比过去
and our traditional architectures again
和我们的传统建筑
just won't accomplish the goal so you
只是不会完成目标，所以你
take ton of all these factors and pour
吸收所有这些因素并倒入
them into a funnel and you have a couple
他们进入一个漏斗，你有几个
of things come out on the top we have
事情出现在我们拥有的顶部
this infrastructure change so we I think
基础设施的变化，所以我认为
most of us recognize that we have not
我们大多数人都知道我们还没有
usually deployed the physical
通常部署物理
architecture for a while we've gone down
一段时间以来我们的建筑
this virtualization journey and some of
虚拟化的旅程以及
us have gone down the journey of moving
我们走了移动的旅程
that into a public cloud I think the
我认为这是一个公共云
journey is carrying us all the way now
旅程一直带我们过去
towards leveraging some form of platform
以利用某种形式的平台
as a service and so that's why I have
作为服务，这就是为什么我有
typical see up here and the nice thing
典型的在这里看到和好东西
about pivotal CF is that I can actually
关于关键CF的是，我实际上可以
deploy my workloads in my data center
在我的数据中心部署我的工作负载
and in a public cloud provider in
并在一个公共云提供商中
exactly the same way by leveraging that
通过利用完全相同的方式
infrastructure but we also have a very
基础设施，但我们也有一个非常
drastic change taking place on the
发生了巨大的变化
application side for many years now we
现在应用端我们已经很多年了
have had this approach of deploying
有这种部署方法
monolithic applications we create what
我们创建的整体应用程序
look like modules but ultimately we
看起来像模块，但最终我们
bound those modules up into a single
将这些模块捆绑为一个
deployable unit and that becomes the
可部署单位，并成为
unit of currency as we actually push
我们实际推动的货币单位
things into a production environment and
东西进入生产环境
as it turns out monoliths do not fare
事实证明，巨石不收费
very well either in an infrastructure
在基础架构中都很好
like clouds or in a realm where we're
就像云层或我们所处的领域
trying to accomplish continuous delivery
试图实现持续交付
and I'll talk about why that is
我会说为什么
but ultimately this is where we're
但最终这就是我们要去的地方
starting to push into this architectural
开始进入这个建筑
style of microservices so in order to
微服务的风格，以便
get the benefits that we have from a
从我们那里获得收益
platform like Cloud Foundry we actually
像Cloud Foundry这样的平台，我们实际上
have to pay some costs and I'm not
必须支付一些费用，而我不是
talking about software licensing cost as
谈论软件许可成本为
much as I'm talking about changing the
正如我在谈论改变
way that I do things so just as an
我做事的方式就像
example cloud foundry optimizes for
示例云铸造厂针对
these things we call 12 factor Linux
这些东西我们称为12因素Linux
applications and I'm not going to go
应用程序，我不会去
through all of the twelve factors this
通过所有十二个因素
morning but if you visit twelve factor
早上，但是如果您参观十二点
dotnet it's a very quick read you can
dotnet，您可以快速阅读
read through all of these in about
仔细阅读所有这些内容
twenty to thirty minutes more than
比二十分钟多三十分钟
likely but just to kind of summarize
可能但只是为了总结
we're talking about for the most part
我们大部分时间都在谈论
very small very focused applications
非常小的非常集中的应用程序
that are stateless meaning that I can
那是无状态的意思，我可以
dispose of them very easily and they
非常容易地处理它们，他们
start up very quickly they shut down
他们很快就关闭了
very cleanly and they late bind to the
非常干净，他们后来绑定到
in configuration information that they
在配置信息中，他们
can discover from their environment so
可以从他们的环境中发现
there's no configuration baked into a
没有配置烘焙到
deployables there's no notion of what
可部署的东西没有什么概念
services I need to contact bacon to the
我需要联系培根的服务
deployables all of that is actually
实际上所有这些都是可部署的
delivered to the application by the
由
platform it's deployed on so this is
它部署在什么平台上
something very different from what we
与我们有很大不同的东西
traditionally built and then micro
传统上建造，然后微型
services themselves are twelve factor
服务本身是十二个因素
Linux applications but they also say a
Linux应用程序，但他们也说
little bit more about the team
有关团队的更多信息
structures that we're going to use what
我们将要使用的结构
the purpose of these application
这些应用程序的目的
services needs to be and also how we're
服务需要以及我们如何
actually going to segregate not just the
实际上不仅要隔离
running code but in many cases how we're
运行代码，但在许多情况下，我们
going to segregate the data in in our
要将我们中的数据隔离
environment and and and all three of
环境和以及所有这三个
those areas including the twelfth factor
那些领域包括第十二个因素
the the typical Enterprise development
典型的企业发展
team is really forced to think about the
团队真的被迫考虑
world a little bit differently
世界有点不同
I like to compare this to when we were
我喜欢将此与我们
trying to adopt agile development
尝试采用敏捷开发
practices around the turn of the century
世纪之交的实践
so at the time extreme programming was
所以当时极限编程是
one of the primary development processes
主要的开发过程之一
that teams were considering and when you
团队正在考虑的问题，以及当您
look at extreme programming you have
看看你有极限编程
this family of 13 practices and these 13
这个家庭的13种习俗，而这13种
practices were expected to be adopted as
预期将采用
a whole but many of us when we would
整个我们当中很多人
come and look at these practices we
来看看这些做法，我们
would selectively adopt the ones that
会选择性地采用那些
either we understand or that we think
我们了解或认为
are applicable to us and we would set
适用于我们，我们会设定
the other practices aside and in many
除了其他做法外
cases when we would do that we would not
在我们会这样做的情况下，我们不会
get the results that we would expect we
得到我们期望的结果
would have we would have failures and
会有我们失败
when you would ask the XP practitioner
当你问XP从业者
why am i failing in this environment
为什么我在这种环境下失败
ultimately the answer would be well you
最终答案会很好
didn't adopt all the practices and the
没有采取所有做法，
reason for that is if you look at the
原因是如果你看
practices as they're as they're drawn on
像被吸引一样练习
the slot here you see there's this
您在这里看到的插槽
network of relationships between them
他们之间的关系网络
the idea is that each of these practices
这个想法是，每种做法
has strengths and weaknesses and it's
有优点和缺点，这是
the combination of the practices and the
做法与
way they support one another in this
他们在这方面互相支持的方式
network that causes them to have a
导致他们拥有
synergistic relationship where the hole
协同关系在哪里
is actually vastly greater than the sum
实际上比总和大得多
of the part and as you start to pull
的一部分，当你开始拉
practices out of this network you
在这个网络之外练习
actually weaken that mesh and make it to
实际上削弱了网格并使其
where it does not do its job nearly as
它几乎没有像
well and I think we find this similar
好吧，我想我们发现这很相似
relationship when we start talking about
当我们开始谈论关系时
platforms like physical CF Cloud Foundry
物理CF Cloud Foundry等平台
and micro services the neither one of
和微服务两者都不是
these environment actually implies the
这些环境实际上意味着
other you can deploy different types of
其他你可以部署不同类型的
architectures to Cloud Foundry but as it
到Cloud Foundry的架构
turns out Micra services are a very
事实证明，Micra服务是一个非常
natural fit
自然适合
to that deployment environment at the
到该部署环境
same time you don't have to be deploying
同时您不必进行部署
to an environment like cloud foundry to
到像Cloud Foundry这样的环境
do micro services but as we'll talk
做微服务，但正如我们所言
about when you adopt this architecture
关于何时采用这种架构
along with all the good things that you
连同你所有的美好事物
get there are several major problems
到达那里有几个主要问题
that you're going to confront that
你将要面对
you're going to have to find solutions
您将不得不找到解决方案
to and again as it turns out a platform
反复地发现一个平台
like cloud foundry it's very much geared
就像云铸造一样，它非常适合
toward solving exactly that set of
完全解决那套
problems so what you end up finding out
问题，所以您最终发现了什么
is that there's sort of symbiotic
是某种共生的东西
relationship between cloud foundry and
云代工厂与
the micro services architecture such
这样的微服务架构
that both actually benefit from being
两者实际上都受益于
used together so what I want to do now
一起使用，所以我现在想做什么
is do a very brief overview of
是对
microcircuits and I want to start by
微电路，我想开始
defining a couple of terms that I use
定义我使用的几个术语
very frequently and those terms are
非常频繁，这些术语是
simple and easy now these seem like
简单和容易，现在这些似乎
words that we use very often and in many
我们经常使用的单词
cases we actually use them
我们实际使用它们的情况
interchangeably so I might call the same
可以互换，所以我可以称呼相同
thing simple and easy when I really mean
我真正的意思是简单易行
essentially the same thing and rich
本质上是一样的东西，丰富
Hickey who is the creator of the closure
封闭的创造者Hickey
language he gave a presentation at the
他在
strange loop conference in 2011 called
在2011年召开的怪圈会议
simple made easy and in that talk he
简单变得容易，在那个谈话中他
wanted to actually tear apart this idea
想把这个想法拆散
that these are interchangeable words and
这些是可互换的单词，
he did this by tracing the origin of
他是通过追踪
these words and he showed that simples
这些话，他表明简单
actually means one folder braid whereas
实际上意味着一个文件夹编织，而
complex means many folds or braids and
复杂意味着很多褶皱或辫子
the idea is that we should be able to
这个想法是，我们应该能够
look at components in an architecture
看架构中的组件
and tell if they are actually decoupled
并告诉他们是否真的解耦了
or if they're coupled or in his words
或如果他们耦合或用他的话
complected together and we should be
一起拼搏，我们应该
able to look at an architecture and get
能够查看架构并获得
the same answer objectively as to
客观上与
whether it's a simple architecture or a
无论是简单的架构还是
complex architecture whereas Easy's very
复杂的架构，而Easy的架构非常
different easy has this notion of things
事物的这种概念与众不同
that line meter to me and obviously what
那条线对我来说很明显
lies near to me is not going to be the
靠近我的谎言不会是
as what lies near to you so when we
就像你附近的东西
think about architectures when we think
当我们思考时考虑架构
about software development we're
关于我们的软件开发
actually thinking about we're thinking
其实在想我们在想
about things that are familiar to us
关于我们熟悉的事情
things that we've done before you know
我们在您知道之前所做的事情
the languages that we've used the
我们使用的语言
frameworks that we've used if I'm a long
如果我很长一段时间，我们使用的框架
term spring developer and you're a long
Spring 学期开发者，您很长
term Ruby developer we might have a very
术语Ruby开发人员，我们可能会有一个非常
different definition for example of easy
不同的定义，例如简单
so I'll use both of these words sort of
所以我会用这两个词
throughout the monolithic architecture
整个整体架构
we don't have to spend a lot of time
我们不必花费很多时间
describing because we're used to it but
描述，因为我们已经习惯了
basically what we're talking about is
基本上我们在说的是
usually some rather large monolithic
通常是一些相当大的整体
relational database it doesn't really
关系数据库并不是真的
matter what being back product is we're
不管是什么退货产品
usually talking about on the other side
通常在另一边谈论
some browser-based client and usually
一些基于浏览器的客户端，通常
what we've built is some combination of
我们建立的是
data access objects and some form of
数据访问对象和某种形式的
service beans regardless of whether
服务bean，无论是否
you're using spring or EJB or something
您正在使用spring或EJB之类的东西
else and we're talking about server-side
其他，我们在谈论服务器端
NBC with server-side templating of
NBC具有服务器端模板
content probably HTML probably some
内容大概HTML大概
smattering of JavaScript if we're really
如果我们真的有一点JavaScript
pushing the envelope maybe we have some
推信封，也许我们有一些
web services API that we can use as an
Web服务API，我们可以将其用作
alternative entry point but in many
替代入口点，但在许多
cases is all we're actually delivering
案例就是我们实际提供的
and so when we think about a monolithic
所以当我们考虑一个整体
architecture like this right off the bat
像这样的架构
I want to describe it as a complex
我想把它形容为复杂
architecture and I want to start as a
建筑，我想从
complex architecture for a couple of
几个复杂的架构
reasons one we're taking all these
原因之一，我们采取所有这些
different modular tiers and we're
不同的模块层，我们
binding them together into a single
将它们绑定在一起
deployables you but not only that we're
可部署您，但不仅仅是我们
taking a whole set of different business
从事一整套不同的业务
concepts from our domain and we're also
来自我们领域的概念，我们也
joining them together into a single
将它们结合在一起
deployable unit so it's very difficult
可部署的单位，所以非常困难
for us to look at this monolith and say
让我们看看这个巨石然后说
that it has seen your focus because it
它已经看到了您的关注，因为
does not but these are very easy for us
不，但是对我们来说这很容易
we're used to this idea of starting a
我们已经习惯了开始
single codebase adding some frameworks
单个代码库添加了一些框架
adding a build process starting to write
添加开始编写的构建过程
code
码
that code overtime until we have again
该代码加班，直到我们再次
all of the knowledge about this
关于此的所有知识
application system in one place we all
一站式应用系统
know that over time they've become more
知道随着时间的流逝，他们变得越来越多
difficult to work with but they're very
很难合作，但是他们非常
easy to get started with one of the
容易上手之一
reasons why these are complex is because
这些复杂的原因是
the tools that we have for modularity
我们拥有的模块化工具
are very difficult to use well they
很难很好地使用它们
require extremely high degree of
要求极高的
discipline so when you think about Java
纪律，所以当您想到Java时
we basically have classes and packages
我们基本上有类和包
and when we use the IDE the ID is very
当我们使用IDE时，ID非常
helpful to us and it will you know
对我们有帮助，您会知道吗
automatically import packages that maybe
自动导入可能
we shouldn't be using or it will
我们不应该使用它，否则它将
automatically allow us to access classes
自动允许我们访问课程
or call methods that maybe we shouldn't
或调用我们可能不应该使用的方法
be using and so if we don't have a high
正在使用，所以如果我们没有高
degree of discipline or we don't have
纪律程度，或者我们没有
tooling in place to sort of detect these
工具到位以检测这些
architectural violations then we can
那么我们就可以违反架构
very quickly create these things that we
很快创造出这些东西，我们
like to call you know spaghetti
喜欢打电话给你知道意大利面
architectures or big balls of mud you
建筑或泥泞的大球你
know whatever term you choose but the
知道您选择的任何术语，但
real difficulty here is even if you are
即使你在这里，真正的困难是
able to keep your modules somewhat
能够使您的模块有所保留
untangled the fact that we're still
我们仍然在纠结
deploying a single monolithic unit is
部署一个整体单元是
problematic and one of the main reasons
有问题的主要原因之一
it's problematic is that it a couple's
有问题的是，这是一对夫妇的
not just the deployment together but
不只是一起部署
also the change cycles so if we have
还有变化的周期，所以如果我们有
multiple business units that are asking
多个业务部门
for functionality and they all go into
功能，它们都进入
this monolith they all have to deploy at
他们都必须部署在这个整体
the same time so if one business unit
同时，如果一个业务部门
has something that it needs today in
今天有需要的东西
order to maintain some competitive
为了保持竞争力
advantage but other coders in flights or
优势，但航班上有其他编码员，或者
other business units that won't be ready
其他尚未准备好的业务部门
for you know a week or two weeks or
因为你知道一个星期或两个星期
longer we actually have to wait or we
我们实际上必须等待更长的时间，否则我们
have to take a great deal of risk in
必须承担很大的风险
order to deploy that and so what this
为了部署它，这又是什么
ultimately turns into is an obstacle to
最终变成一个障碍
deploying more frequently which is
更加频繁地部署
something we desperately want to be able
我们迫切希望能够做到的事情
to do
去做
in order to keep that iterative
为了保持迭代
innovation feedback cycle actually
创新反馈周期实际上
moving but also we have this idea that
移动，但我们也有这样的想法
scaling is inoffensive so we said we
缩放是无礼的，所以我们说我们
have more users we need to be able to
有更多的用户，我们需要能够
scale but obviously some areas of our
规模，但显然我们的某些领域
app are going to be hit more heavily
应用将受到更大的打击
than other areas of our application and
比我们应用程序的其他领域
if we're deploying the monolith we don't
如果我们要部署整体，我们就不会
have the choice in most cases to scale
在大多数情况下可以选择扩展
only portions of that application we
只有该应用程序的一部分
actually have to scale all of it or none
实际上必须全部缩放或不缩放
of it as we start to do that we start to
我们开始这样做的时候，我们开始
waste resources another problem that we
浪费资源是我们另一个问题
run into here is these monolithic
碰到这里就是这些单片
architectures as they grow inside they
建筑在内部成长
can be very intimidating to new
对新手可能会非常吓人
developers joining a team so if you walk
开发人员加入团队，所以如果你走
in the door as a new developer and
作为新开发者进入
you're confronted with a schema with a
您面对的是带有
couple of thousand cables and a couple
几千根电缆和几根
of thousand hibernate classes and then a
一千个休眠类，然后一个
whole layer of service beans and
整个服务 bean 层和
controllers and screens on top of that
控制器和屏幕之上
it can be very difficult to be
很难成为
productive because not only are you
富有成效，因为不仅您
learning this architecture you're
学习这种架构
learning a new business domain you're
学习您正在使用的新业务领域
perhaps learning a new set of frameworks
也许学习一套新的框架
you're learning the people that you're
你正在学习你所要的人
working with and almost all of those
与几乎所有这些一起工作
areas are just a large degree of
面积很大
complexity that you have to be familiar
您必须熟悉的复杂性
with so it can be very difficult to
因此很难
start getting your job done so this
开始完成工作，所以这
becomes an obstacle to scaling
成为扩展的障碍
development on so one of the ways that
如此发展的一种方式
we would like to be able to go faster is
我们希望能够走得更快
to do more work in parallel and we can
同时进行更多工作，我们可以
do more work in parallel if we have more
如果我们有更多的工作并行
people but I think more of most of us
人，但我认为我们大多数人
are familiar with the experience of
熟悉
throwing more and more people into the
把越来越多的人投入
same development sandbox and finding out
相同的开发沙箱并找出
that the more people we add the less
我们增加的人越少
actually gets done and a lot of that can
实际上已经完成，很多可以
actually be traced to the monolithic
实际上可以追溯到整体
architecture as we'll see in a moment
我们稍后会看到的架构
and then finally there's this idea of
最后有这个想法
adopting new technology which is very
采用非常新的技术
very difficult for us in a monolithic
对于我们来说非常困难
world and the reason for that is as we
世界，其原因是因为我们
adopt new technology we're actually
采用我们真正的新技术
attaching them to these monolithic
将它们附加到这些整体式
architectures meaning that more of the
架构意味着更多
businesses functionality is
业务功能是
actually accepting the risk of bringing
实际接受带来的风险
that technology in the door and this is
在门上的技术，这是
one of the reasons why we have a hard
我们努力奋斗的原因之一
time and a lot of pushback against
时间和很多反对
adopting technologies that might be
采用可能是
appropriate tools to solve a problem
解决问题的适当工具
that we have in front of us so when we
在我们面前，所以当我们
look at the micro service architecture
看一下微服务架构
it looks very different and just walking
看起来很不一样，只是走路
across this slide in the middle we see
在中间的这张幻灯片上，我们看到
that we have broken the monolith up into
我们已经将整体分解成
a set of different services so we have
一套不同的服务，所以我们有
three different types of services here
三种不同类型的服务
deployed a few instances deployed of
部署了一些实例
each and the two on the top have HTTP
每个和顶部的两个都有HTTP
interfaces this is probably a rest
接口，这可能是休息
interface the service in the bottom in
在底部连接服务
green is an asynchronously driven
绿色是异步驱动的
service so we have an AMQP message
服务，因此我们收到AMQP消息
broker like rabbit and Q sitting in the
像兔子和Q这样的经纪人坐在
middle of the architecture and divvying
建筑的中间和令人陶醉
up work amongst these services if you go
如果您去的话，在这些服务中加紧工作
to the far left of the diagram you see
在您看到的图表的最左侧
that we're acknowledging this reality
我们承认这个现实
that we have a diversity of climates if
如果我们有多种气候
you go to the far right side of the
你去的最右边
diagram you see that not only have we
图表中，您不仅看到我们
broken up with services but we've also
与服务分手，但我们也
broken up the data so each of these
分解数据，以便每个
services is governing its own piece of
服务正在管理自己的一部分
the business domains data and in many
业务领域数据以及许多
cases it's actually doing that using a
情况实际上是使用
specially selected database technology
特选的数据库技术
that fits its query and rewrite patterns
适合其查询和重写模式
in a very appropriate way and in between
以一种非常合适的方式
the clients and the Micra services
客户和Micra服务
themselves we see this long vertical bar
自己，我们看到了这条长长的竖线
here this represents what I call an API
这代表了我所说的API
gateway and the API gateways job is to
网关和API网关的工作是
perform tasks like service aggregation
执行诸如服务聚合之类的任务
reduce the chattiness between the
减少之间的聊天
clients and the micro services and do
客户与微服务并做
things like protocol translation and the
协议翻译和
main reason for this is that as we break
主要原因是当我们休息时
up our environment into all these micro
把我们的环境融入所有这些微观
services if all of our clients aren't
如果不是我们所有的客户都可以提供服务
say for example our phones need to know
例如说我们的电话需要知道
about 40 50 100 150 services to get
约40 50 100 150的服务获得
their job done
他们的工作完成了
we're going to have a high degree of
我们将高度重视
latency in displaying screens we have a
显示屏幕的延迟
lot of network traffic and ultimately
大量的网络流量，最终
that's going to lead to a poor user
这将导致不良的用户
experience and many cases is actually
经验，很多情况是
going to kill the battery on a lot of
会杀死很多电池
these devices which is of critical
这些设备至关重要
importance so we think about
重要，所以我们考虑
microservices and and right out of the
微服务，然后就可以了
gate I'm going to contrast them by model
门，我要按型号对比它们
it with monolith by calling them simple
通过将其称为简单来实现
and they're simple because as you saw
它们很简单，因为如您所见
we're taking all of the different
我们正在采取所有不同的方法
concerns that we have in the
我们所关注的
architecture and we're forcing a hard
建筑，我们正在努力
boundary of separation between them but
它们之间的分离边界，但是
I call them hard because this is very
我打电话给他们，因为这非常
different from how we traditionally
与我们传统上的方式不同
worked and there's a lot of challenges
工作，有很多挑战
that we're going to face that maybe we
我们要面对的也许是我们
haven't faced before and we'll talk
没遇到过，我们再谈
about those a little bit later but we do
关于那些事，但是我们做
have a new and better tool for
有一个更好的新工具
modularity and that is that we force an
模块化，那就是我们强迫
API boundary between all of our services
我们所有服务之间的API边界
so that it's no longer just a method
这样它不再只是一种方法
call way to get to some business logic
调用一些业务逻辑的方法
it's actually a network call way to get
实际上是通过网络致电的方式
to that business logic and it makes
该业务逻辑，它使
maintaining those architectural
保持那些建筑
boundaries a lot easier because it's a
边界容易得多，因为它是
lot bit more difficult to make those
很难使那些
types of calls by mistakes and instant
错误和即时通话的类型
by injecting a little bit of pain into
通过注入一点点痛苦
the process we actually make it easier
我们实际上使它更容易的过程
for us to keep a clean architecture in
让我们保持整洁的架构
place and because we do that we keep our
的地方，因为我们这样做，所以我们保持我们的
change cycles be coupled so those
变更周期要结合在一起
business units that we talked about
我们讨论的业务部门
before those business units are able to
在那些业务部门能够
deploy their services when they need
在需要时部署他们的服务
them which means that they can go faster
他们，这意味着他们可以走得更快
they can keep that feedback wheel
他们可以保持反馈轮
actually spinning and I can scale more
实际旋转，我可以扩大规模
efficiently so if one business unit
高效，所以如果一个业务部门
service is getting hit very hard by
服务受到了很大的打击
demand and the other services are not I
需求和其他服务不是我
simply scale up that one business unit
只需扩大一个业务部门
service to handle that demand and I use
服务来满足这种需求，我用
my resources a lot more efficiently and
我的资源更有效地
then when I join a team like this as a
然后当我加入像这样的团队
new developer I'm joining a smaller team
新开发人员我正在加入一个较小的团队
with the smaller code base a smaller
代码基数越小，代码越小
data model that I need to learn and so I
我需要学习的数据模型，所以我
have a lot
有很多
more chance of being productive more
更多的机会更有生产力
quickly because the whole architecture
很快，因为整个架构
that I face as I walk through the door
我走进门时面对的是
is a lot less intimidating and this also
少了很多吓人，这也
enables us to scale development by
使我们能够通过
parallelizing by adding more people
通过增加人员来并行化
because instead of throwing everybody
因为而不是扔给大家
into a single sandbox I can actually
可以放进一个沙盒中
just create more sand boxes and and
只需创建更多的沙箱，然后
divide up into smaller teams and finally
分成较小的团队，最后
adopting new technology for developers
为开发人员采用新技术
and architects becomes much less risky
建筑师的风险大大降低
because I can adopt that new technology
因为我可以采用这项新技术
within a single micro-service and I'll
在一个微服务中，我将
usually pick a micro service that is a
通常选择一个微服务
little less risky a little less critical
风险少一点，关键一点
to the business and try and trial that
尝试并试用
technology there and if things work out
技术在那里，如果一切顺利
great I can start to roll that across
太好了，我可以开始
the rest of the micro services but if
其余的微服务，但如果
things don't work out and I fail my
事情没有解决，我失败了
failure is fairly cheap and I can
失败相当便宜，我可以
actually back that out without affecting
实际上将其退出而不影响
a huge amount of the business so the
大量的业务，所以
question that comes up then is how do we
那么出现的问题是我们如何
actually divide this up and a very
其实把它分成一个非常
important guiding principle here is
这里重要的指导原则是
what's called Conway's law so nolan
所谓的康威定律
connolly wrote down this statement in
connolly在下面写下了这个声明
1957 he said an organization that design
1957年，他说一个组织
the system is going to produce a design
该系统将产生一个设计
whose structure is a copy of the
其结构是
organization's communication structure
组织的沟通结构
and so I challenge you to take a look at
所以我挑战你来看看
your architecture and actually compare
您的架构并进行实际比较
it to the way you're actually organized
它以您实际组织的方式
in working and see if you actually know
在工作，看看你是否真的知道
this this very striking similarity
这非常惊人的相似
between the way people are organized and
在人们的组织方式与
the way code gets organized if we think
如果我们认为，代码的组织方式
about the way that we traditionally
关于我们传统上的方式
organize technical people we usually do
组织我们通常做的技术人员
it by specialization so we take all the
通过专业化，所以我们把所有
DBAs and we put them on a team would
DBA，我们将它们放在一个团队中
take all the middleware specialists we
带走我们所有的中间件专家
put them on a team we take all the UI
将他们放在团队中，我们采用所有UI
specialists and we put them on a team
专家，我们将他们放在团队中
and not surprisingly when we group these
并且当我们将这些分组时并不奇怪
individuals together into project teams
个人一起组成项目团队
those individuals recreate those siloed
那些人重新创造那些孤岛
architectures
建筑
within that mana with that we end up the
在那法力之内，我们最终
plane so creating a micro service type
平面，因此创建微服务类型
architecture using this kind of
使用这种架构
organization is going to be very
组织将会非常
difficult if not impossible so the idea
困难甚至不可能，所以这个主意
is to actually start to organize your
是实际上开始组织您的
teams based on the architecture that you
基于您的架构的团队
want to produce and some friends of mine
想生产和我的一些朋友
have actually called this the inverse
实际上称其为逆
Conway maneuver this idea of creating an
康威（Conway）操纵创建一个
ideal architecture that we want to
我们想要的理想架构
achieve and then structuring our teams
实现并组建我们的团队
around business capabilities that will
围绕业务能力
carry us to that architecture these
这些带我们到那个架构
business capability teams have all of
业务能力团队拥有所有
the roles necessary for delivering not a
交付的必要角色
project that delivers that capability
提供这种能力的项目
but a product that delivers that
但是可以提供
capability C project teams are ephemeral
能力C项目团队是临时的
when the project is done they're usually
当项目完成时，他们通常是
disbanded whereas product teams survive
解散，而产品团队生存
throughout the lifetime of a product and
在产品的整个生命周期中
they're responsible for understanding
他们负责理解
the requirements building that
建立需求
capability develop deploy net capability
能力发展部署网络能力
and running that capability and
并运行该功能，
maintaining it in production basically
基本上保持生产
until that capability is no longer
直到那种能力不再
needed and these teams not sure if
需要，这些团队不确定
you're familiar with this idea of two
您熟悉两个这样的想法
pizza teams it was popularized by Amazon
比萨队被亚马逊推广
or this idea that if a team can't be fed
或者说如果一个团队无法满足
with only two pizzas than the team is
比团队只有两个披萨
too big and that's sort of the size that
太大了，差不多
were we're talking about so how do you
我们在谈论什么，你怎么样
actually decide what the partitions are
实际决定什么是分区
so in many cases there are a lot of
所以在很多情况下
tools that you can use a simple tool
您可以使用简单工具的工具
that folks will use is this idea of
人们会使用的是这个想法
nouns and verbs so looking for the nouns
名词和动词，所以寻找名词
and those become my service factors
这些成为我的服务因素
looking for verbs those become my
寻找那些成为我的动词
service founders but ultimately this is
服务创始人，但最终这是
a fairly simplistic tool and has
一个相当简单的工具，并具有
somewhat limited utility another thing
实用性有限
that you can look at is the single
你可以看到的是单
responsibility principle or this idea
责任原则或这个想法
that a component any architecture should
任何架构的组件都应该
it do only one thing not only one
它只会做一件事，而不只是一件事
responsibility and in many cases this is
责任，在许多情况下，这是
defined
定义的
it should have only one reason to change
它只有一个改变的理由
and and this can work for us if we don't
如果我们不这样做，这可以为我们工作
get too bogged down and agreeing on what
陷入困境，就什么达成共识
exactly is a reason to change so it's
正是改变的原因，所以
all I'm seeing used very successfully to
我所看到的一切都非常成功地用于
do these partitions is this idea of a
做这些分区是这个想法
bounded context from domain driven
域驱动的有限上下文
design or this idea that essentially
设计或这种想法
there is no one domain model that can
没有一个领域模型可以
actually describe all of the data that
实际描述所有数据
your business wants to think about
您的企业想考虑
because ultimately you're going to have
因为最终您将拥有
cross-cutting concepts in that domain
该领域中的跨领域概念
that have slightly different semantics
语义略有不同
in different contexts so we're looking
在不同的情况下，所以我们正在寻找
at here is a domain model for a movie
这是电影的领域模型
distribution business and so on the left
分销业务等
hand side we have this product catalog
手侧，我们有此产品目录
service the product catalog service
服务产品目录服务
thinks about movies but when they think
考虑电影，但当他们想到
about movies it's thinking about the
关于电影的思考
actual motion picture itself you know
您知道的实际电影本身
that has a title that has actors and
标题中包含演员和
actresses directors genre associated
女演员导演类型相关
with it the system on the right is an
有了它，右边的系统是
inventory system and the inventory
库存系统和库存
system also thinks of movies but it
系统也会想到电影，但是
thinks of them in the context of kind of
在某种情况下想到他们
gluing a name to a piece of media DVD
将名称粘贴到一张媒体DVD
that we have a certain number of in we
我们有一定数量的
have those numbers in different
这些数字不同
locations so I know where these movies
位置，所以我知道这些电影在哪里
are and how many of them I have and and
是，我有多少，以及
how many are in circulation and so on so
有多少在流通中，依此类推
I could attempt to model both of these
我可以尝试为这两个模型
in a single system and mash all of them
在一个系统中并将其全部合并
and there'll be many other concepts
还有很多其他的概念
within a system like this that need to
在这样的系统中
represent movies and I can mash them all
代表电影，我可以将它们全部融合
together into a single domain model and
一起成为一个单一域模型
movies going to become this very large
电影将变得非常大
concept that sometimes we'll call it
有时我们会称之为的概念
like a god object for example and
像神的物体，例如
anything that anytime we need to change
任何时候我们需要改变的东西
the system we're likely going to need to
我们可能需要的系统
go through a movie so instead what we're
看电影，所以我们是
doing here is we're drawing these
在这里做的是我们正在画这些
bounded context around
周围的有限上下文
product catalog and inventory and we're
产品目录和库存，我们
basically saying let movie mean what
基本上说让电影意味着什么
movie means to the product catalog and
电影是指产品目录和
let movie mean what movie means to the
让电影意味着电影对
inventory system and then create
库存系统，然后创建
lightweight integration points between
之间的轻量级集成点
them such that I can map a movie in one
他们，以便我可以将一部电影映射
context onto a movie in another context
在另一上下文中将电影上下文
but then not force each of these
但不要强迫这些
contexts to consider the other context
考虑其他上下文的上下文
definitions of that term so when we do
该术语的定义，所以当我们这样做时
this we can start to think of our
我们可以开始思考我们的
services and the data that these
服务和这些数据
services govern our as bounded context
服务控制着我们的有限环境
and when we do that we create this API
当我们这样做时，我们将创建此API
boundary but it doesn't just protect the
边界，但它不仅保护
code but it also protects the data and
代码，但它也可以保护数据和
not just the data but the representation
不只是数据，还有表示
and the storage technology associated
和相关的存储技术
with that data so we can start to adopt
有了这些数据，我们就可以开始采用
this idea of polyglot persistence or
多语言持久性的想法或
using the data store that's most
使用最多的数据存储
appropriate to the job that we're trying
适合我们正在尝试的工作
to get with the job that we're trying to
得到我们想要的工作
do so how do we actually integrate these
这样做我们如何真正整合这些
services now and this is the point where
现在服务，这就是
I like to explain this is not so much a
我想解释的不是那么多
new architecture it's just a reframing
新架构，这只是一种重新设计
of a very old architecture and we find
非常古老的建筑，我们发现
its origins in a sense in this idea of
从某种意义上说，它的起源
UNIX and and pipes and filters so when
UNIX和管道以及过滤器，因此
we look at Unix UNIX is primarily
我们来看Unix UNIX主要是
structured that environment is
结构化的环境是
structured as a set of very focused very
构造为一组非常专注的
small programs that do one thing and do
做一件事情并做的小程序
one thing well and the way we create
一件事以及我们创造的方式
integrations that use multiple programs
使用多个程序的集成
is by linking them together through
是通过将它们链接在一起
these pipes and redirects and the
这些管道和重定向以及
integration mechanism is actually quite
整合机制其实相当
dumb in that these pipes they don't know
愚蠢的是，他们不知道这些管道
anything about the data that is
关于数据的任何事情
traveling through them all they're doing
遍历他们所做的一切
is linking the output stream of one
正在链接一个的输出流
process to the input stream of another
处理到另一个的输入流
process and all the smarts that allow me
过程和所有允许我的智慧
to actually deal with
实际处理
the data flowing through that mechanism
通过该机制的数据流
actually acts ends up in the end points
实际行为最终会终结
and this is very different from how
这与如何
we've traditionally implemented service
我们传统上实施了服务
based architectures using things like
基于架构的东西
ESB s so in an ESB we tend to put all
ESB，因此在ESB中，我们倾向于将所有
the smarts in the communication
沟通中的聪明人
mechanism and the services tend to not
机制和服务往往不
have a lot of knowledge of the world
对世界有很多了解
around them whereas in this style of an
在他们周围，而在这种风格
architecture it's actually the inverse
架构实际上是相反的
of that we put the smarts and the
其中，我们把聪明人和
endpoints and the integration mechanism
端点和整合机制
does not have a lot of knowledge about
没有太多的知识
the services that it's actually joining
它实际上正在加入的服务
together and a colleague of mine Neil
和我的同事尼尔在一起
Ford describes this as choreography of
福特将其描述为
orchestration so orchestration is this
编排是这样的
idea of central control where we have a
集中控制的想法
large heavyweight bus that is
大型的重量级巴士
representing all the policy all the
代表所有政策
integration and rousing logic and it
集成和唤醒逻辑及其
actually is governing the architecture
实际上是在控制架构
and anytime we need to make a change to
在任何时候我们需要改变
the overall system we end up very often
整个系统，我们经常被淘汰
touching this enterprise service bus
触摸此企业服务总线
which if you open up looks again like a
如果您打开它，看起来又像
boiling pot of spaghetti and it hides a
沸腾的意大利面锅，它隐藏了
lot of the complexities in the
许多复杂的
architecture whereas with microservices
体系结构而使用微服务
we're actually exposing the complexity
我们实际上是在揭示复杂性
in the architecture and placing the
在架构中并放置
smarts and the endpoint allowing them to
智能和端点，使他们能够
choreograph their interaction so it's
编排他们的互动，所以
very much like the comparison of the
非常像
orchestra to the ballet so when you go
芭蕾舞团的乐团，所以当你去
to the orchestra you have a director
到乐团你有导演
standing in front of the musicians
站在音乐家面前
that's telling them what to do and he
告诉他们该怎么办，他
takes the place of the ESB and in the
取代ESB，并在
services based architecture whereas when
基于服务的架构，而何时
we look at the ballet a there is no
我们看芭蕾舞，没有
central control during a performance and
表演期间的中央控制
the actual dancers have to adapt and and
实际的舞者必须适应和
and in some cases change their behavior
在某些情况下会改变他们的行为
in order to have a successful
为了成功
performance and that's what we find in
性能，这就是我们发现的
these micro services based architectures
这些基于微服务的架构
where the services themselves are
服务本身在哪里
actually responsible for their
实际上对他们负责
integration we
整合我们
is the surrounding ecosystem which is a
是周围的生态系统
nice segue into this idea that none of
很好地了解了这个想法，
this is a free lunch so Ben Wooten
这是免费的午餐，所以Ben Wooten
several months ago published a really
几个月前发表了一个
great article at high scalability titled
高伸缩性的好文章
microcircuits is not a free lunch and in
微型电路不是免费的午餐
that article he itemizes a whole lot of
那篇文章他列举了很多
the difficulties that we run into when
我们遇到的困难
we deploy architectures like this so
我们部署这样的架构
obviously we're deploying many more
显然，我们正在部署更多
things in an architecture like this in
像这样的架构中的事物
many cases if we fully adopt it we're
很多情况下，如果我们完全采用它，
delivering many more technologies
提供更多技术
simultaneously and we've also created a
同时，我们还创建了一个
distributed system and distributed
分布式系统和分布式
system carry their own sets of
系统携带自己的套
complexity and this is not free we have
复杂性，这不是免费的，我们有
to increase our discipline in many cases
在许多情况下增加我们的纪律
we have to pay for a much more
我们必须付出更多
significant operations overhead so
大量的运营开销
there's a lot more things that we have
我们还有很多东西
to do to keep this infrastructure alive
保持基础架构的生命力
not the least of which is this idea that
最重要的是这个想法
it's very difficult to monitor one of
监视其中之一非常困难
these architectures whereas monitoring a
这些架构，而监控
monolith is actually relatively
整体而言实际上是相对的
straightforward and we have to have a
直接，我们必须有一个
very strong cultural relationship
牢固的文化关系
between development operations if these
在开发操作之间，如果这些
are not already in place and we have
还没有到位，我们有
other challenges of our testing
测试的其他挑战
strategies that work with monolith don't
适用于整体的策略不会
necessarily work very well and martin
一定工作得很好，马丁
fowler carries this a little bit further
福勒将这一点更进一步
with this idea of if you think about the
如果您考虑
carnival ride with the sign that says
嘉年华骑着标语
you must be this tall to ride the ride
你必须高个子才能骑
he makes this statement that you must be
他说你必须
this tall to use microcircuits that
这么高的微电路
there's just a few basic disciplines
只有一些基本学科
that you're going to have to have in
你将不得不拥有
place to be able to build and deploy and
能够构建和部署的地方
keep alive an architecture like this so
保持这样的架构，这样
being able to provision new environments
能够提供新的环境
very rapidly with the runtime stacks the
运行时堆栈很快
middleware stacks the data services
中间件堆叠数据服务
the method brokers that you need to be
您需要成为的方法经纪人
able to develop and test the stage and
能够开发和测试舞台，并且
ultimately run in production these
最终将这些产品投入生产
systems and you have to be very good at
系统，您必须非常擅长
monitoring not just the apps themselves
不仅监控应用本身
but also the emergent interactions in
而且在
this distributed system and you have to
这个分布式系统，您必须
be able to turn application deployment
能够进行应用程序部署
very very quickly because as you're
非常非常快，因为
deploying more in smaller bits if you're
如果您愿意，可以在较小的部分部署更多
if your deployment process is
如果您的部署过程是
bottlenecking you you're not going to
瓶颈，你不会
get the benefits that you want and then
得到想要的好处，然后
just this idea of a collaborative DevOps
只是这种协作式DevOps的想法
culture where we're all working together
我们一起工作的文化
towards shared goals with you know
与您达成共同的目标
shared incentive strategies to actually
共享激励策略
get us to be focused not on the goals of
让我们专注于目标
our individual silos but the goals of
我们各自的孤岛，但目标
actually moving that concept to cash
实际上将这个概念转变为现金
relationship forward so there's a lot of
关系向前发展，所以有很多
organizational issues here and and and
组织问题，以及
and with technology I can't fix
和技术，我无法修复
organizational issues but there's a lot
组织问题，但是有很多
of technical issues that we also have to
我们还必须解决的技术问题
solve and so one of the main things that
解决，所以主要的事情之一
we're doing a pivotal with Cloud Foundry
我们正在与Cloud Foundry合作
and with Spring is we're building a
而与Spring合作，我们正在建立一个
platform to make it possible to solve a
解决问题的平台
lot of these technical problems of being
这些存在的许多技术问题
able to provision being able to maintain
能够提供能够维持
applications and monitor those
应用程序并监视那些
applications and so if you look at a lot
应用程序，所以如果你看很多
of the features that you find in cloud
在云中找到的功能
foundry like being able to rapidly and
铸造厂喜欢能够迅速
consistently provision environments and
持续提供环境
being able to scale up both on demand
能够按需扩大规模
and automatically application instances
并自动应用程序实例
and being able to maintain the health of
并能够保持健康
those apps and if they fail restart them
这些应用程序，如果它们失败，请重新启动它们
and be able to handle complex routing
并能够处理复杂的路由
and load balancing in a very performant
并在非常出色的负载平衡
way being able to run your Mongo and
能够运行您的Mongo和
Cassandra and adieu and wrap it into an
卡桑德拉（Cassandra）和阿迪耶（adieu）并将其包装成一个
elastic sir
弹性先生
and all these other services that you
以及您提供的所有其他服务
want to bring to the table in these
想带到这些桌子上
architectures and then being able to get
架构，然后能够获得
real-time monitoring information about
实时监控信息
what are the latency characteristics of
的延迟特性是什么
my services
我的服务
how are my errors error rates what is my
我的错误率是多少我的错误率是多少
request volume look like but there's
请求量看起来像，但是有
also a set of blower plate patterns that
还有一组鼓风模式
we need to be able to to deal with it
我们需要能够处理它
come out of these these distributed
从这些散布出来的
systems now being able to have a
系统现在能够拥有
distributed version configuration and
分布式版本配置和
being able to do things like service
能够做诸如服务之类的事情
registration and discovery so that we
注册和发现，以便我们
can glue these things together and being
可以将这些东西粘合在一起并被
able to integrate these services and and
能够集成这些服务，以及
then as we deploy more things we have
然后随着我们部署更多的东西
more chances for failure so being able
更多失败的机会，因此能够
to build fault tolerant architectures
建立容错架构
and being able to configure these things
并能够配置这些东西
through asynchronous messaging and have
通过异步消息传递并拥有
configuration changes trickle through an
配置更改通过
entire architecture in a very standard
以非常标准的整体架构
way so this is what spring cloud is
这样，这就是 Spring 的云
actually bringing to the table and an
实际上带到桌子上
umbrella set of projects to help us
一揽子项目，以帮助我们
realize those boilerplate patterns and
实现那些样板模式并
one of the ways that it's doing that is
它这样做的方法之一是
by starting to wrap a lot of the
通过开始包装很多
boilerplate solutions to these problems
这些问题的样板解决方案
that have been open sourced by Netflix
Netflix开源的
so Netflix has been one of the sort of
所以Netflix就是其中一种
poster children for this micro services
此微服务的海报儿童
architecture and in doing that they
建筑，这样做
solved a lot of these problems
解决了很多这些问题
themselves and in very compelling ways
自己并且以非常引人注目的方式
and what we're dealing with spring cloud
以及我们正在处理的 Spring Cloud
is making these solutions very very
使这些解决方案非常非常
palatable to consume for a spring
美味可口
developers so very quickly as I sort of
开发人员是如此之快
shut down I want to just show a very
关闭，我只想展示一个非常
brief demo of a three micro service
三种微服务的简短演示
architecture that's in action that's
运作中的架构
running on Cloud Foundry and it is using
在Cloud Foundry上运行并且正在使用
the service discovery and the fault
服务发现与故障
tolerance and the routing capabilities
公差和走线能力
that are inherent in sprint cloud so if
这是sprint云中固有的
I if I go over to the brown
我如果我去棕色
over here you'll see digital web
在这里，您会看到数字网络
services which is our public service
服务是我们的公共服务
that we run of Condry that you can sign
我们经营的Condry您可以签署
up for and get a free trial to to try
争取免费试用
out and I have all the applications and
出来，我有所有的应用程序，
as well as my Eureka and my history
以及我的尤里卡和我的历史
dashboard service and my configuration
仪表板服务和我的配置
service deployed as apps on Cloud
服务部署为云上的应用程序
Foundry I also have RabbitMQ and MongoDB
铸造厂我也有RabbitMQ和MongoDB
provision as services that I can use in
提供作为我可以在其中使用的服务
this in this infrastructure so if we
在这个基础架构中，如果我们
look again at the architecture which is
再看一下架构
actually embedded in the app we see that
实际上嵌入到应用程序中，我们看到
we have a customer service we have a
我们有一个客户服务，我们有一个
store service and then we have a user
商店服务，然后我们有一个用户
interface service that's actually in a
界面服务实际上在
sense linking those things together so
感觉将这些东西联系在一起
the question is is how do these services
问题是这些服务如何
actually know that each other exists so
实际上知道彼此存在，所以
that's salt through Eureka which is a
通过尤里卡盐，这是一个
service registry and discovery engine
服务注册表和发现引擎
and basically what you see here is that
基本上，您在这里看到的是
as all these applications are coming up
随着所有这些应用程序的到来
they're registering themselves with this
他们正在为此进行注册
Eureka server so I can see that here's
尤里卡服务器，所以我可以看到这是
my config server my customer service my
我的配置服务器我的客户服务我的
UI my storage service now how did those
UI我的存储服务现在如何
get there well if you go and look at my
到那里好吧，如果你去看看我的
screen spring application my config
屏幕Spring 应用程序我的配置
server actually deployed my config
服务器实际上部署了我的配置
server has a spring boot application
服务器具有Spring Boot应用程序
simply by annotating it with a naval
只需用海军注释
config server but then to make it
配置服务器，但然后使其
register with Eureka
向尤里卡注册
I simply annotated it one more time with
我只是简单地再注释一次
enable Eureka client my Eureka server
为我的Eureka服务器启用Eureka客户端
itself is deployed by creating a spring
通过创建Spring 来部署自身
boot application again those these are
再次启动应用程序，这些是
basically one class very small apps and
基本上是一类非常小的应用程序，
I'm enabling Eureka server to get that
我正在启用Eureka服务器来实现这一点
deployed so again when my customer
当我的客户再次部署
service comes up I'm again saying enable
服务启动，我再次说启用
Eureka client so in all those cases
尤里卡客户，所以在所有这些情况下
these services end up being registered
这些服务最终被注册
here so now let's talk a bit about what
在这里，现在让我们谈谈什么
the
的
the service actually does so if I go
如果我去的话，服务实际上是这样做的
look at my customers here you notice I
看看我的顾客，你会注意到我
have one customer in place in San
在San有一位客户
Francisco name's James waters if I drill
如果我钻探，弗朗西斯科名字叫詹姆斯·沃特斯
down into his record I can see his
深入他的记录，我可以看到他的
location
位置
but I also see all of the Starbucks
但我也看到了所有的星巴克
stores that are that are nearby to to
附近的商店
James and this information is actually
詹姆斯，这些信息实际上是
coming to the UI through a hyper media
通过超媒体进入用户界面
interface that's created by spring data
由spring数据创建的接口
rest are I'm sorry I'm spring hey Yas in
休息，对不起，我是 Spring ，嘿，亚斯
this case so so this bit right here is
这种情况，所以这是这里
the data that's maintained by the
维护的数据
customer service but all of the store
客户服务，但所有商店
data is maintained by the store service
数据由商店服务维护
and is represented in the customer
并代表客户
service by a hyperlink so if I took this
通过超链接服务，所以如果我带这个
hyperlink and I drop it into another
超链接，然后将其放入另一个
browser window you see all the stores
浏览器窗口中您会看到所有商店
coming up so the question is is what
来了，所以问题是
would happen if the stores service were
如果商店服务是
to go down if you go back to the
如果你回到
architecture diagram you see that we're
架构图，您看到我们
actually coming to the customer service
真正来到客户服务
bill load balancer called ribbon which
票据负载均衡器称为功能区
is actually also tying into you don't
其实也跟你绑在一起
see it on this architecture a a circuit
在此架构上看到它的电路
breaker called hysteresis and basically
断路器称为磁滞，基本上
what that's doing is protecting my
这是在保护我
dependency from cascading failures so I
从级联失败的依赖，所以我
have a monitor that actually tells me
有一台显示器实际上告诉我
you know what is the health of the link
你知道链接的健康状况吗
between the customer service and the
在客户服务和
store service and I can find that in
商店服务，我可以在
this store integration class I have a
我有这个商店整合课程
method here that's creating that
这里创建的方法
hyperlink called get stores by location
名为按位置获取商店的超链接
and the way I turn that circuit breaker
以及我打开那个断路器的方式
on is simply by annotating it with
只需简单地用
history's command and providing a
历史命令并提供
fallback method so when this circuit is
后备方法，因此当此电路为
is is tripped to open meaning that I've
被绊倒了意味着我已经
detected to my dependency is unhealthy
发现我的依赖不健康
said I'll get this fallback behavior
说我会得到这种后备行为
which is to return null and that's going
这将返回null，这将
to have the effect of turning that store
可以去那家商店
list off so let's just test that out
列出来，让我们来测试一下
I'll go to the command line and I'll
我将转到命令行，然后
kick off the shell script that's going
启动将要运行的shell脚本
to really bang on my customer service
真正打动我的客户服务
significantly and if I go back here you
重要的是，如果我回到这里，你
see that the number of requests is
看到请求数是
actually increasing fairly rapidly the
实际上增长很快
circuits closed and all these requests
电路关闭，所有这些请求
are healthy so I'm now going to induce a
是健康的，所以我现在要诱导
failure in the architecture by telling
通过告诉架构失败
Cloud Foundry to stop the store service
Cloud Foundry停止商店服务
so Cloud Foundry has now stopped the
因此Cloud Foundry现在已停止
store service if you notice in the top
如果您注意到顶部的商店服务
pane the hyperlink representing stores
窗格代表商店的超链接
went away because we're returning null
走了，因为我们返回null
from that method and that also has the
从这种方法，也有
effect of in the user interface if I
如果我在用户界面中的效果
again go back to customers we see that
再次回到客户，我们看到
there are no stores anymore for James if
如果没有詹姆斯的商店了，如果
I look at my history monitor I see that
我看着历史记录监视器
my circuit has been tripped to open and
我的电路已跳开，
I'm intercepting all these requests now
我现在正在拦截所有这些请求
in responding with default behaviors
用默认行为回应
occasionally I will actually hold the
偶尔我会实际持有
dependent service to see if it's healthy
依赖服务以查看其是否健康
again so you'll see the number of errors
再次，因此您将看到错误数量
go up to one two or three but then we'll
上升到一二或三，但是我们会
put back into a state where we're
回到我们所处的状态
responding with null so if I want to
用null响应，所以如果我想
resuscitate now the store service and do
现在恢复商店服务并执行
that
那
and as the store service is starting
随着商店服务的开始
back up we can go back over to the
备份，我们可以回到
history dashboard and we can continue to
历史信息中心，我们可以继续
watch that
看那个
you
您
and in just a moment we're going to see
片刻之后，我们将看到
it trip the back to closed
它跳回关闭
so the circuit is now closed again and
因此，电路现在再次关闭，
we're seeing successful requests to the
我们收到了对
storage service if you look at the
存储服务，如果您查看
terminal you see that the store's
终端，您会看到商店的
hyperlink is back in place and then if
超链接回到原位，然后如果
we go back to the UI we see that we have
我们回到用户界面，我们看到
also recovered our our functionality
也恢复了我们的功能
it's no longer turned off okay so that
不再关闭了，这样
was a quick demo of the spring cloud
是 Spring Cloud 的快速演示
stuff I want to finish up with just
我想要完成的东西
about three more slides before we go to
我们去之前大约还有三张幻灯片
questions and just this idea that this
问题，只是这个想法
architecture micro service is well it's
体系结构微服务很好
not entirely new the this style of
不完全是这种风格
delivering services is is relatively
提供服务是相对的
different from what we've seen in the
与我们在
past few years and it's really the first
过去的几年，这实际上是第一个
architectural style that has shown up
展现出来的建筑风格
post the continuous delivery
过帐连续交付
conversation posts the DevOps
对话发布DevOps
conversation so you take a bunch of
谈话，所以你花了一堆
teams that are thinking about the ideals
考虑理想的团队
of how do we do continuous delivery and
我们如何进行持续交付
how do we do DevOps and you see the
我们如何做DevOps，您会看到
architectural style that they're
他们的建筑风格
developing and in many many many cases
发展中，在许多情况下
what's popping out is what we're now
突然出现的就是我们现在的样子
calling micro services and one of the
调用微服务和
reasons for this is that we have a very
原因是我们有一个非常
operational focus we've had service
我们提供服务的运营重点
based discussions for a long time but in
长时间的讨论，但是
many cases they have not only been
很多情况下，他们不仅
effective on the whiteboard and again my
在白板上有效，再次在我的
colleague needle he makes the statement
他发表声明的同事
that architecture is abstract until it's
该架构是抽象的，直到
been operationalized it was very easy
投入运营非常容易
for us to draw the ESD
给我们画ESD
on the whiteboard and it looks very good
在白板上，看起来非常好
but when we actually went out and tried
但是当我们实际上出去尝试
to deploy and operate this and then do
进行部署和操作，然后执行
things like continuous delivery with it
像这样连续交付
ultimately because it was not will
最终因为不是那样
operationalized those architectures so
将这些架构投入运营
over so my corollary to that statement
因此，我对该陈述的推论
is that architectures that are not
是那些不是
operationalized they really effectively
他们真正有效地运作了
exists only on whiteboards what we get
仅存在于白板上
in
在
practice is actually something that is
实践实际上是
far less effective and so ultimately
效果不佳，因此最终
what we're trying to do by compiling
我们正在尝试通过编译来做什么
microservices with pivotal Cloud Foundry
具有关键Cloud Foundry的微服务
with spring clouds what we're trying to
随着 Spring 的云，我们试图
create for ourselves is this idea of an
为自己创造是这个想法
operationalized architecture so that we
可操作的架构，以便我们
can effectively do DevOps so that we can
可以有效地进行DevOps，以便我们可以
effectively do continuous delivery and
有效地进行持续交付并
ultimately so that we can again speed up
最终使我们可以再次加速
that innovation cycle and be able to
创新周期并能够
shorten concept to cache and deliver
缩短要缓存和交付的概念
value to our customers a lot more
为我们的客户带来更多价值
quickly so that's the end of the
很快，这就是结束
prepared presentation so I think we can
准备演讲，我想我们可以
take whatever a little bit of time we
花一点时间我们
have left and drop into a QA awesome
已经离开并加入了质量检查
thanks Matt can you hear me I can hear
谢谢，马特，你能听到我吗？
you great Peter okay fabulous um so we
彼得，你好极了，嗯，所以我们
don't have any questions at the moment
目前没有任何问题
but one of the ones that I've heard
但我听到的其中一个
being it's spring one and one of the
是 Spring 的第一场
ones I hear you know out with you and
那些我听说你知道你和
and out with other people talking about
和其他人谈论
this stuff is your dewy well actually we
这个东西实际上是你的露水
do have one question coming in but on
确实有一个问题来了
let me park that for one second um you
让我把它停一秒钟
know what what are some of the and maybe
知道是什么，也许
don't you don't spend too much minute
你不花太多时间
meant but you know allotted Microsystems
的意思，但你知道分配的微系统
micro services are kind of a darling
微服务有点像宠儿
architecture right now a lot of people
现在的建筑很多人
talking about it not always a lot of
谈论它并不总是很多
people talking about the the pitfalls
人们谈论陷阱
and they talk about the goodness but you
他们谈论善良，但是你
know what are some of the challenges
知道有哪些挑战
that you're going to run into trying to
你会遇到尝试
adopt this this this architecture and
采用这种架构
this organization structure to your
您的组织结构
earlier point on and how does it has you
前面的观点以及它对你的影响
know it has needed to solve those things
知道它需要解决这些问题
or like in what you know what's the
或喜欢你所知道的
relationship there yeah so I'm
那里的关系是的，所以我
ultimately what it boils down to is what
最终归结为
primary challenges if you're not good at
如果您不擅长主要挑战
stamping out environments um already and
已经淘汰了环境，并且
because the real thing here is we're
因为真正的事情是我们
wanting to go fast
想要快点
it's hard enough to go fast with one
跟一个人走下去很难走
thing it's a lot harder to go fast with
事情要走快要困难得多
10 things and it's even more difficult
10件事，甚至更困难
to go fast with a hundred things and so
快速处理一百件事
ultimately in order to be able to do
最终为了能够做
that well and then be able to handle you
好，然后能够处理你
know all these distributed systems
了解所有这些分布式系统
concerns is show up and things like
担忧正在显现，诸如此类的事情
eventual consistency and things like
最终的一致性和类似的东西
fault tolerance you just you have to
容错能力，您只需要
deal with a lot of concerns that you
处理您的许多担忧
didn't have before and whether you adopt
以前没有，你是否采用
a off the shelf has platform or not to
现成的有平台或没有平台
help you solve those problems you're
帮助您解决自己的问题
going to have to have a platform and so
必须要有一个平台等等
if you look at what Netflix did you know
如果你看一下Netflix你知道什么
they decided you know we're going to you
他们决定你知道我们要去你身边
know make supporting an Amazon Web
知道使支持Amazon Web
Services centric architecture a core
以服务为中心的架构是核心
competency for us and we're going to you
我们的能力，我们要去找你
know really you know seek out building a
知道真的，你知道寻找建立一个
comment base within the company of tens
数十家公司内部的评论库
or hundreds of people that are focused
或数百人专注
on making that work well and what do
使该工作顺利进行以及做什么
they do they went they built a platform
他们去了他们建立了一个平台
so if you can do that and if that's one
所以如果你能做到的话
of your goals great most companies are
大多数公司的目标是
never actually going to go do that most
从来没有真正去做那件事
companies are going to say ok I can't
公司会说好，我不能
adopt this architecture it's too hard or
采用这种架构太难了
they're going to say I've got to go get
他们会说我必须去得到
something that like what Netflix built
像Netflix建立的东西
but somebody's going to have to build it
但有人要建造它
for me and so in any case that's where a
对我来说，所以无论如何
platform like cloud foundry comes into
像云铸造这样的平台
play because I can take that and I can
玩，因为我可以接受，我可以
run it and I can have companies like you
运行它，我可以拥有像你这样的公司
know because it'll help me run that and
知道，因为它将帮助我运行该程序，
understand how to get that up and
了解如何起床并
running so that I can go focus on
运行，以便我可以专注于
building apps and let Cloud Foundry you
构建应用程序，让Cloud Foundry帮助您
know focus on you know getting those
知道专注于你知道得到那些
environments built out and and letting
建立和出租的环境
spring cloud help me deal with all those
Spring 的云帮助我处理所有这些
distributed system concerns and that's
分布式系统问题，那就是
not something that Amazon really handles
不是亚马逊真正处理的事情
that was something the Netflix had built
那是Netflix建立的
your point yeah right right exactly
你的观点是正确的正确的
thanks for that yeah absolutely um ok
谢谢，是的，绝对很好
cool a Praveen Kumar asks
酷Praveen Kumar问
how will filtering be done in this
如何在此进行过滤
architecture you know usually you have
你通常知道的建筑
big sequel with all the filters and
有所有筛选器和
where clause but since you can't join
where子句，但由于您无法加入
the data between the micro-services at
微服务之间的数据位于
the database layer you know you kind of
您知道的数据库层
have to do this in the application he
必须在应用程序中执行此操作
thinks you know is there if that's true
认为你知道那是真的吗
you know is there a performance impact
您知道对性能有影响吗
that I think this is a great question
我认为这是一个很好的问题
one I think I've heard a lot that was
我想我听到过很多
the other sort of what I was going to
我要去的另一种
mention so wait a way to provide for
提及，所以等待一种方法来提供
asking but you know as you were seeing
问，但你知道你所看到的
earlier the different micro-services
较早的不同的微服务
kind of own their own data right you
拥有自己的数据对吧
know how do you you you know what
知道你如何你知道
eventual consistency like you know how
最终的一致性，如您所知
does that dealt with and what's the
处理了什么，这是什么
performance impact it's a praveen's
对性能的影响是普遍的
question yeah this is uh this is a huge
问题是的，这是一个巨大的问题
issue that you have to deal deal with
您必须处理的问题
and ultimately again it boils down to
最终又归结为
that concept that you know every time
你每次都知道的概念
you get something you have to pay
你得到一些你必须付钱的东西
something and so so your your what
某物，所以你是你的什么
you're doing is you're taking a lot of
你在做的是你在做很多事情
capability that we kind of mash down and
我们融合在一起的能力
let the database player take care of for
让数据库播放器为
us and we're saying okay well you know
我们，我们说的很好，你知道
we're going to manage that elsewhere
我们将在其他地方进行管理
because now we have all these different
因为现在我们有所有这些不同
data services that are that have things
有东西的数据服务
in front of them it's like okay I want
在他们面前，就像我想要的一样
to do I want to ask a question or I want
我想问一个问题还是我想
to deliver a screen that's going to
提供要转到的屏幕
touch a bunch of these different things
碰一堆这些不同的东西
and so if you do that kind of naively
所以如果你这么天真地做
and say okay well I've got my little
说好吧，我有我的小东西
mobile app and I'm going to call the
移动应用，我将调用
first service and get some data and I'm
第一次服务并获取一些数据，我
going to call the second service and get
要打电话给第二个服务并获得
some data and then somehow lunge all
一些数据，然后以某种方式刺入所有
that into what I want to display to my
我想展示给我的东西
user you're going to you're going to
用户，您要去，您要去
you're going to die a very painful death
你会死得很痛苦
of frustration in trying to make that
试图使之沮丧
work so so that API gateway pattern that
这样工作，以便API网关模式
I talked about on on the earlier slide
我在较早的幻灯片上谈到了
and I can actually throw that back on
我实际上可以把它放回去
the screen very quickly now is actually
现在屏幕很快
playing a lot of that role so so what
扮演很多角色，那又如何
that API gateways job is doing is for
API网关的工作是为了
one of these apps so you know not this
这些应用之一，所以你不知道这个
isn't a this is not an ESP this is not a
不是这不是ESP这不是
monolithic thing if you what you usually
单片的东西，如果你平时
see and has
看到并拥有
especially on Netflix use this is that
特别是在Netflix上，这是
each of their different device in points
每个不同设备的得分
whether it was an iPhone or a you know
无论是iPhone还是您知道的
an Xbox or a set-top box whether it is
Xbox或机顶盒，无论是
it needs to conceive consume these back
它需要设想消耗掉这些
in services and so they would build one
在服务中，所以他们会建立一个
of these gateways whose job is to sort
这些网关的工作是进行排序
of act like you know my little my own
就像你知道我的小我自己
little API for that device and what it
该设备的小API及其功能
what that API looks like are the types
该API的外观是类型
of queries that I would have made in
我本应进行的查询
many cases that monolithic system and so
很多情况下，整体系统等等
the key is within the guts of that API
关键在于该API的精髓
gateway and and so much like you know
网关等等，就像您知道的一样
you would have a database deciding how
您将拥有一个数据库来决定如何
to most efficiently join all of these
最有效地加入所有这些
tables together this API gateway that
将这个API网关
you're writing is now deciding how to
您正在写的内容正在决定如何
efficiently join the results of all
有效地加入所有结果
these microservices calls so that's
这些微服务调用，所以
super important to be able to do that
能够做到这一点非常重要
parallel in parallel concurrently very
并行并行并行
well and so this is where you start to
好，这就是您开始的地方
see a lot of the adoption of these these
看到这些的很多采用
reactive patterns that that we're
我们的反应模式
starting to enable more and more with
开始越来越多地与
things like reactor and you know new
像电抗器之类的东西，你知道新的
additions to spring integration and
Spring 集成的补充和
other things that you can build and also
您可以建立的其他东西
you're going to see other tool kits for
您将看到其他工具套件
this you know come out of the of the
这你知道从
Cloud Foundry space for helping to build
Cloud Foundry空间可帮助构建
these gateways and so it's job is
这些网关，所以它的工作是
essentially to kind of do the joins and
本质上是做连接和
the transformation aggregation of
的转化聚集
content and make it look like to these
内容并使其看起来像这些
these clients that that we're still kind
这些客户我们仍然很友善
of doing things the old way for getting
做事的老方法
the benefits of decoupling everything on
将所有事物解耦的好处
the backside let make sense yep yep yep
背面让有意义是的是的
nice I like that thank you and just a
很好，我喜欢，谢谢，只是
quick side note I thought what was
快速旁注，我以为是
really cool that a demo was a the way it
演示非常有趣
failed gracefully right when you know
当您知道时，优雅地失败
when you when you kill the store service
当您杀死商店服务时
but you know you didn't get some like
但是你知道你没有得到像
nasty you know 500 error you know boy
讨厌，你知道500错误，你知道男孩
yeah yeah Green you know it's just just
是啊绿色你知道这只是
that piece of it didn't work and I just
那部分没有用，我只是
thought that was really cool
以为真的很酷
yeah next question from Jeff James he
是的，Jeff James的下一个问题是
asks how can you validate up front a
问您如何预先验证
whole microservice architecture in
整个微服务架构
particular the granularity that services
特别是服务的粒度
now Matt I know you talked about this
现在，马特，我知道你谈到了这个
earlier with the single responsibility
较早时负有单一责任
principle and you know the nouns and the
原理，你知道名词和
verbs and you know some of the other
动词，你知道其他一些
things but maybe just a teeny bit more
的东西，但也许只是一点点
on that because we're actually getting a
之所以这样，是因为我们实际上得到了
few more questions so I don't want to
还有几个问题，所以我不想
spend too much time on it as we already
我们已经花了太多时间
do cover it a little bit so how do you
掩盖一点，那你如何
validate that you're basically doing the
验证您基本上是在做
TKE decomposition correctly yeah yeah he
TKE分解正确，是的，他
said he phrases it the granularity of
说他说这是粒度
the services which I take to me you know
我带给我的服务你知道
the decomp is it's it's very challenging
decomp是非常有挑战性的
and it's hard to give a quick and fast
而且很难快速给出
answer but one thing I can tell you is
回答，但我可以告诉你的一件事是
what not to do which is don't start
做什么不开始
seeking you know numbers of lines of
寻找你知道的行数
code or numbers of you know verbs or
您知道动词或
service calls or things in the in the
服务电话或
service because ultimately what you're
服务，因为最终您是什么
going to end up doing is creating
最终要做的就是创造
artificial decomposition and you're
人工分解，你
going to be creating service granularity
将要创建服务粒度
that's probably more extensive than what
那可能比什么更广泛
you want but you're going to see
你想要，但你会看到
articles out there and say oh yeah a
那里的文章说哦是的
micro service should only be 150 lines
微服务只能是150行
of code or less and that's just as
或更少的代码，就像
fallacious as when we would say that you
谬论，就像我们会说你
know a java method should be only you
知道一个Java方法应该只有你一个
know 30 lines and if it's 31 lines it's
知道30行，如果是31行
too long you know so so juristic like
太久了，你知道这么法理
that are actually quite ineffective
实际上是无效的
really what it boils down to is you know
归根结底是你知道
thinking about what is the minimum size
考虑最小尺寸是多少
of a capability that's actually going to
实际上要去的能力
deliver real business value to the
为企业带来真正的商业价值
architecture and and and for some
架构和
capabilities that's going to be 150
能力将达到150
lines of code for some capabilities that
一些功能的代码行
might be a couple of thousand lines of
可能是几千行
code it you know yes you have to really
编码它，您知道是的，您必须真正
focus on you know what is the thing duty
专注于你知道职责是什么
and what is its job in the architecture
以及它在架构中的工作是什么
and ultimately you know if if I need to
最终你知道我是否需要
do something very differently tomorrow
明天做点很不一样的事情
you know is is this thing keep going to
你知道这是继续
keep getting hit and if it is I probably
不断受到打击，如果是的话，我可能
need to decompose it so it's really
需要分解，所以它真的
focus on change and and and what are you
专注于变化，而你又是什么
trying to accomplish
试图完成
yeah it's hi and this is a hard one to
是的，这很喜，
answer I agree and I totally read it
回答我同意，我已经读完了
like to go to the wrong way to look at
喜欢以错误的方式看待
it because like you know that's so they
因为就像你知道那样
mean you know you put in a good
意思是你知道你投入了一个好
framework like spring boots and what
像 spring boot 之类的框架
does that really mean yes you know
这真的意味着是的，你知道吗
they're all right let me you know and
他们很好，让我知道
then you know that so that's highly
那么你知道那是非常重要的
framework dependent inside like school
像学校一样依赖框架
dependent and then you know you watch
依赖，然后你知道你在看
that Adrian Cockcroft interview on info
Adrian Cockcroft对信息的采访
cue you know I think it was it was like
提示你知道我想那是
30 minutes Long's one of Charles humbles
30分钟，查尔斯·朗斯（Charles Long）谦虚
trembles videos with him and you know
和他一起颤抖，你知道
when he was talking about this you know
当他谈论这个时，你知道
it means he made it community very clear
这意味着他让社区变得非常清晰
that sort of the art in the science you
你科学中的那种艺术
know and this is where this is a this is
知道，这就是这里，这是
not a you know there isn't like a
不，你知道那里不像
prescriptive way to go about this so I
规范性的方式来解决这个问题，所以我
don't it's a really tough one to answer
难道这是一个很难回答的问题
and yeah thanks for taking a stab at it
是的，谢谢你为此付出一点代价
I appreciate it um the next question
我感谢下一个问题
comes up I'm going to skip ravine again
出现，我将再次跳过山沟
just because he already had one question
只是因为他已经有一个问题
that he asked and just make sure I catch
他问，只是确保我抓住了
the others um Daniel applaud asks how
丹尼尔鼓掌的其他人问
does a micro service architecture
做一个微服务架构
perform in near real-time applications I
在近实时应用中执行
because it's interesting cuz you were
因为你很有趣
just mentioning reactor yeah how do we
刚才提到反应堆是的，我们该怎么办
perform a meal near real-time
近乎实时地做饭
applications um you know it's I'm not
应用程序，你知道我不是
really a hundred percent sure what we're
真的有百分之一百确定我们是什么
talking about here because to me when I
在这里谈论，因为当我
think of my primary goal when I'm
想起我的主要目标
fielding something like this is I'm
像这样的东西是我
thinking of the person that is you know
想着你认识的人
holding a phone and trying to get a
拿着电话，试图得到一个
response to some question very you know
回答一些问题，你知道
you know it what do we tolerate when
你知道当我们忍受什么
when we're dealing with with our phones
当我们处理手机时
you know if response time is anywhere
你知道响应时间是否在任何地方
you know greater than a second many
你知道不止一二
times we start to get
时代我们开始得到
straighted right so around I think you
伸直，所以我想你
know again it really boils down to how
再次知道它真的归结为
you're building your edge services is
您正在建立边缘服务是
going to govern your performance so they
决定你的表现，所以他们
don't end ok yeah why what is why I
不要结束，是的，为什么是为什么我
suspect what I smell behind his question
怀疑我在他的问题后面闻到了什么
here is is not necessarily what's the
这不一定是什么
like you know the Google 250 millisecond
就像您知道Google的250毫秒
or whatever you know 350 millisecond or
或任何您知道的350毫秒或
whatever low barrier to glass for the
玻璃的低阻隔
end user device but more on you know
最终用户设备，但您知道更多
either
要么
machine machine communication or more
机器机器通讯或更多
like Internet of Things you know hi oh
就像物联网，你知道哦
yeah
是的
that that's that's kind of what I'm
那就是我的那种
smelling he wasn't specific but in
闻到他不是很具体，但是
chanyeol if you're still in the line and
chanyeol（如果您仍在排队）
you want to clarify please feel free but
您想澄清一下，请随意
that that was what I was smelling a
那就是我闻到的
little bit I could be wrong but well
一点我可能是错的，但是很好
yeah and and and that's that's a I mean
是的，那就是我的意思
that's a huge concern too because you
这也是一个很大的问题，因为您
know if you think about service to
知道你是否考虑服务
service communication you have to start
您必须开始的服务沟通
to think about network and network
考虑网络和网络
distance and a number of pops and you
距离和一些持久性有机污染物，你
know it's just another proof point that
知道这只是另一个证明
you know a having a very strong
你知道一个非常强大的
operational discipline that is working
运作中的运作纪律
in dovetail with your with your team
与您的团队相吻合
that's actually developing the apps and
这实际上是在开发应用程序，
services you know so that we understand
您知道的服务，以便我们了解
that you know we're not making bad or
你知道我们没有变坏
poor decisions about how we're laying
关于我们如何安排的错误决定
things out and then ultimately you know
事情出来，然后最终你知道
having a platform you know like a Cloud
有一个像云一样的平台
Foundry that's going to make a lot of
铸造将使很多
those decisions for me and and and
这些决定对我和
control a lot of that that that traffic
控制很多流量
routing for me so that so that I have
为我路由，以便我有
the good decisions sort of made on my
对我做出的好决定
behalf but then there's another kind of
代表，但是还有另一种
more subtle point that is you know
你知道的更微妙的一点
related to how we actually decide to
与我们实际决定
make service calls so you know obviously
拨打服务电话，以便您清楚地知道
a network call is more expensive than a
网络通话比
method call so if all I did was take the
方法调用，所以如果我所做的就是
method calls I was making to the service
我对服务进行的方法调用
that's you know running in process with
那就是你知道正在运行
me I divide those up and I turn all
我我将它们分开，然后全部
those method calls in the network calls
网络调用中的那些方法调用
it's going to fall over pretty quickly
它会很快掉下来
so there's
所以有
kind of spectrum between coarse and fine
粗糙和精细之间的光谱
grained communication and we kind of
细粒度的沟通，我们有点
went down that path when we did EJ B's
当我们做EJ B的时候走了那条路
you know like 15-20 years ago of you
你知道像你15到20年前
know we want to start to make very
知道我们要开始变得非常
coarse screen calls and because we're
粗屏电话，因为我们
doing all these remote we thought we're
做所有这些遥远的事情，我们以为我们
gonna have all these remote beans
将拥有所有这些远程 bean
floating around and we're going to be
飘来飞去，我们将成为
communicating between them and we're
他们之间的沟通，我们
doing you know it's a bit a very high
你知道这有点很高吗
level of abstraction we're doing the
我们正在做的抽象级别
same type of stuff so you know this idea
一样的东西，所以你知道这个主意
we're going to take a bunch of methods
我们将采取一系列方法
and generate a rest and if I arrest
休息一下，如果我逮捕
interface but generate some web
界面，但生成一些网页
inter-services interface from it and
它之间的服务间接口
it's just going to work is actually
只是去上班实际上
going to turn into a high degree of
会变成高度
frustration so you really need to think
沮丧，所以你真的需要思考
about you know how much work can I get
关于你，我能得到多少工作
done in a call and that's going to drive
在通话中完成，这将推动
a lot of that performance characteristic
许多性能特征
and I think I think a synchrony can help
而且我认为我认为同步可以有所帮助
there a little bit easily now stuff like
现在有点容易
stuff like reactor and you know I think
像反应堆这样的东西，你知道我认为
you know there's other third-party
你知道还有其他第三方
things out there like rx Java and you
那里的东西，例如Rx Java和您
know in Scala and stuff like that but
知道在Scala之类的东西，但是
but yeah that you know I think there is
但是，是的，你知道我认为有
a good natural fit between asynchronous
异步之间的良好自然契合
processing and you know and micro
处理，你知道和微
services I think those are a very nice
我认为这些服务非常好
fit actually um for a number of reasons
实际上适合um的原因有很多
but ok cool um sorry I don't mean to you
但是好吧，嗯，对不起，我不是对你
know kind of gloss over it it's just
知道它的光泽只是
that we're getting a whole bunch more
我们得到了一大堆
questions now all of a sudden and sir
现在突然问先生
we're already 15 minutes after the hour
我们已经下班了15分钟
Matt one idea just to handle some of the
马特（Matt）一个想法只是为了处理一些
flow here might be that you know we take
这里的流可能是你知道我们采取
questions and maybe you kind of you know
问题，也许你知道
we you and I work on them after the
我们和您一起工作之后
webinar and post some of the answers to
网络研讨会并将一些答案发布到
your blog or something like that just
您的博客或类似的东西
gives a bunch of them are coming in but
给了一堆他们进来，但
anyway let me move on to the next one on
无论如何，让我继续下一个
let's see um we talk about near
让我们看看我们在附近谈论
real-time oh yeah
实时哦，是的
Henry Wang has any guidelines or
亨利·王有任何指导方针或
suggestions to transform a monolithic
改造整体的建议
half into micro services the million
微服务一半投入百万
dollar question way to go Harry oh sure
美元问题的解决方法哈里
yeah that's not something that I talk
是的，那不是我所说的
about almost every time I get into a
几乎每次我进入
white board discussion with you know one
与您讨论白板讨论
of the customers that we're working with
与我们合作的客户中
yeah so so so I'll do it
是的，所以我会做的
as I can the first thing you do in my
我可以做的第一件事
mind is you draw a line in the sand and
介意你是在沙子上划一条线
say okay everything that we do this net
说好吧，我们做这个网的一切
knew that we would have normally gone in
知道我们通常会进去
and attached a new function to this
并为此附加了新功能
monolith we're going to create a
整体，我们将创建一个
microservice representation of that and
的微服务表示和
in order to do that we're going to have
为了做到这一点，我们将不得不
to integrate the two so one of the
整合两者，所以其中之一
things that I see is you build this idea
我看到的是你建立了这个想法
of an anti-corruption layer that
的反腐败层
protects that microservice from being
保护该微服务
too tightly bound to the monolith and
太紧密地绑定到整体
sort of brokers the communication
经纪人之间的沟通
between the two and that can be just
在两者之间，那可能仅仅是
another service API and in a lot of
另一个服务API以及很多
cases you can use sort of the gateways
您可以使用各种网关的情况
and things that spring integration to
以及与之融为一体的事物
great effect to help provide that
效果很好，可以提供
insulation so so you get good at
绝缘，所以你会擅长
delivering that new functionality as
提供新功能
microservices first and and once you you
微服务，一旦您
kind of got that discipline down then
然后把那种纪律放下
it's on the trip saying okay how can I
在旅途中说可以，我该怎么办
start to break this thing up and so you
开始分解这件事，所以你
need another decision guide there and
需要另一个决策指南
that is you know what are the things
那就是你知道那是什么东西
that are changing most because
变化最大的原因是
ultimately the things that are changing
最终改变的事物
the most are the things that you want to
最重要的是你想要的东西
be able to deliver continuously and so
能够持续交付，因此
those are the things that are being
这些就是正在发生的事情
inhibited the most by being attached to
被依恋最大
that monolith so then you start to say
那块巨石，所以你开始说
okay let's find modules that make sense
好吧，让我们找到有意义的模块
that really need to change and again
真的需要改变一次
chunk those off into new money for
把那些变成新钱
services and build further
服务并进一步发展
anti-corruption layers to kind of
反腐败层
integrate those two things together and
将这两件事整合在一起
then as you're consuming those common
然后当你消费那些普通的
services that that you chunked off
您分拆的服务
redirect them to the micro service
将它们重定向到微服务
representation instead of you know the
代表而不是你知道
monoliths representation of that so
这样的整体表示
you'll do that for a period of time and
你会做一段时间
you're going to you're going to reach
你要去你要达到
two possible endpoints one endpoint is
两个可能的端点，一个端点是
you decompose the whole thing and and
您分解了整个事物，并且
you're done and you can actually start
您完成了，您实际上可以开始了
to remove those anti corruption layer
去除那些反腐败层
because you don't need them anymore
因为你不再需要它们了
another possible end point is you've
另一个可能的终点是
actually reached the point where you're
实际上达到了你的目的
no longer going to get a huge amount of
不再会得到大量的
value from doing further decomposition
进一步分解的价值
because the services that you've left
因为您留下的服务
behind are actually they're not changing
后面实际上是他们没有改变
very much they're kind of done and you
他们已经完成了，而你
just don't really feel the need so you
只是真的没有感觉到需要所以你
might leave a certain skeletal portion
可能会留下一定的骨骼部分
of that monolith behind that you know
你知道的那块巨石的
has an API layer to it and then
有一个API层，然后
everything else is moving forward or
其他一切都在前进，或者
maybe you find some services that you
也许您会找到一些服务
just don't need anymore and you can
只是不需要了，你可以
simply delete but that that's kind of
只需删除即可，但这有点
the process that I walk through with
我经历的过程
people and it seems to work well there's
人，而且似乎运作良好
actually if you if you google around a
实际上，如果您在Google周围搜索
little bit and maybe we could even put
一点，也许我们甚至可以放
out some links in some some notes later
在一些注释中列出一些链接
on to some different case studies people
在一些不同的案例研究中
have posted of walking through that
发布了通过
exact process with their architecture
他们的架构的确切过程
very cold Matt Thanks um I think I think
马特，谢谢，我觉得我很冷
if we can do one or two more we still
如果我们能再做一两个，我们仍然
still have almost 50 people on the line
仍然有将近50个人
from from a hundred so it seems like
从一百开始
these are good questions maybe we'll
这些是很好的问题，也许我们会
just do one or two more and and before
再做一两个，然后
we call it a call it a session here and
我们称其为“会话”，
then you know we'll do this again at
那么您知道我们会在
10:00 a.m. okay effect by the way if
上午10:00还可以，如果
there are folks that you know really are
有些人你真的知道
hot to get some questions answered and
急于回答一些问题，并且
you want to join us again please feel
您想再次加入我们，请感到
free to come to the set towards the end
快到集结了
of the second session um so let's see
第二届会议的时间，所以让我们来看看
hopefully this is a little bit more of a
希望这是更多的
yes/no question Praveen Kumar asks again
是/否问题Praveen Kumar再次询问
he says is the service registry
他说是服务注册中心
discovery that you mentioned in spring
你在 Spring 提到的发现
cloud is that an implementation of the
云是
Gateway pattern there's a lot of things
网关模式有很多东西
called the Gateway pattern so I'm not
称为网关模式，所以我不是
necessarily sure which one you're
一定要确定你是哪一个
referring to but I wouldn't characterize
指，但我不会描述
it as one myself you know the service
作为一个我自己，你知道服务
that Eureka that spring cloud is is sort
那个 Spring 的云是尤里卡那种
of wrapping for us is not actually
为我们包装实际上不是
gating any traffic between the the
闸门之间的所有流量
instances or services it's it's all it's
实例或服务就是全部
doing is you know allowing services to
您是否知道允许服务
announce themselves and then allowing
宣布自己，然后允许
other services to query and see what
其他服务查询，看看有什么
services are available but once I kind
服务是可用的，但一旦我亲切
of obtain that information then I'm
获得这些信息，然后我
actually going directly point-to-point
实际上直接进行点对点
with with those things yep yep and then
与那些东西是的，然后
while we're wrapping up here on would
当我们在这里总结
you bring up the roadshow page up on
您打开了路演页面
your desktop browser so there ya folks
您的桌面浏览器，所以有你们
can can look at that and no problem and
可以看一下，没问题，
I'll speak to that in a minute um while
我待会儿再说
you're doing that let me tea up the next
你这样做是让我下一个下午
question for you because I know that's
向您提问，因为我知道那是
probably fairly brainless um let's see
可能是相当无脑的嗯，让我们来看看
do to do so many a lot of good questions
要做很多很多好的问题
here thanks guys this is awesome um uh
在这里，谢谢大家，这很棒
what are some consequences of the data
数据有什么后果
model translations between bounded
有界之间的模型翻译
contest
比赛
one texts asks GC well I think the I
一个文本问GC好我想我
think there's there's two huge
认为那里有两个巨大的地方
consequences out of the gate the first
后果出局第一
consequent that could be a whole other
因此，这可能是一个整体
presentation in itself is you know how
演示本身就是您知道如何
do you start to think about
你开始思考吗
transactional behaviors across all these
所有这些的交易行为
data services because in some cases
数据服务，因为在某些情况下
you're going to have to start to you
你将不得不开始
know if you really want to go that way
知道你是否真的想那样走
you're going to be thinking about
你会在想
distributed transaction vanessa whole
分布式事务Vanessa整个
huge rabbit full of spells and in some
满是咒语的大兔子
cases that's not even going to be
甚至不会的情况
possible and you're really going to have
可能，你真的将拥有
to start to get comfortable with you
开始适应你
know architectures around eventual
了解最终的架构
consistency and you know what are the
一致性，你知道什么是
implications that there and then their
暗示那里，然后他们
their their patterns and things like
他们的模式和诸如此类的东西
event sourcing and command query
事件源和命令查询
responsibilities segregation lots of
职责隔离
patterns that if you need that
如果您需要的模式
complexity you can start to go down that
您可以开始降低复杂性
road to help you deal with some of those
帮助您应对其中一些问题的途径
things but you're ultimately going to
事情，但你最终会去
confront some level of that and then
面对某种程度的然后
another one of the consequences that
另一个后果是
you're going to run into right out of
你会马上遇到
the gate is okay
大门还可以
i want to ask questions like from a
我想问一个类似的问题
reporting mindset like i wanna i want to
报告我想要的心态
discover something about what's that
发现那是什么
they've been to my overall behavior that
他们去过我的整体行为
normally i would have asked you know i
通常我会问你知道我
would have written some arbitrary sequel
会写一些任意的续集
query to my database and all the data
查询我的数据库和所有数据
would have been there it would have
本来在那里
joined and different back to each of
加盟，并不同回到每个
that question now i can't do that so am
这个问题现在我不能那样做
i making API calls to all these services
我对所有这些服务进行API调用
hopefully not so this is where there's
希望不是这样，这是那里
some menu patterns for creating sort of
一些菜单模式，用于创建
you know sidecar reporting database
你知道Sidecar报告数据库
structures to get this done i talked
结构，我说过做到这一点
about this a little bit of spring one of
关于 Spring 的一点点之一
this idea of you know as things are
你的想法就是事物
happening in your services of venting
您的放空服务中发生的事情
out those things to a message bus so
把那些东西放到消息总线上
that you can feed them into something
你可以把它们喂进东西
like for example i'll lamda architecture
例如，我将使用lamda建筑
which again i don't have time to go into
再次，我没有时间去
but you can you can query for lamda
但您可以查询lamda
orchids
兰花
and you'll see all sorts of resources of
然后您会看到各种资源
this idea of basically putting
这个基本的想法
everything that's ever happened into
曾经发生的一切
some long-term archives or like for
一些长期档案或喜欢
example HDFS and then being able to
HDFS示例，然后能够
write you know things like MapReduce
写你知道像MapReduce这样的东西
jobs to to answer those questions in a
工作来回答这些问题
batch form but also kind of having a
批处理形式，但也有
streaming layer and something that I
流媒体层和我
might use a spring XD for to do some
可能会使用spring XD做一些
real-time analytics on that data as it's
对数据进行实时分析
changing so you know they're they're
变化，所以你知道他们是他们
basically you still have to do at a high
基本上你仍然需要付出高昂的代价
level all the things you always wanted
平整您一直想要的所有东西
to do but because you changed your
去做，但是因为你改变了你的
architecture the solutions to those
为那些架构解决方案
problems look very different in some in
问题看起来有些不同
some cases just substantially different
有些情况大不相同
but because we know we still have to do
但是因为我们知道我们仍然要做
them we're solving the problem so as you
他们我们正在解决问题，以便您
decompose the data those are a couple of
分解那些数据是
the main things you're going to run into
您将要遇到的主要事情
not the only things that there's we can
不只是我们能做的
go to go on a whole you know discussion
去进行一个整体，你知道讨论
for a probably another hour or two yes
再大概一两个小时
there absolutely and it's funny actually
绝对有，而且很有趣
one of the other attendees Jeff James
其他与会者之一Jeff James
had asked specifically you consider you
曾特别询问过您是否认为您
know command query CQRS an event
知道命令查询CQRS事件
sourcing is valid options so that that's
采购是有效的选择，因此
then you kind of I'm really happy you
那你我真的很高兴
touched on that Thanks oh yeah yeah and
感动了，谢谢哦，是的，
if you need if you need that complexity
如果需要，则需要这种复杂性
absolutely you know sounds like a good
绝对你知道听起来不错
fit for for micro service architecture
适用于微服务架构
but no yeah anyway so I think we're
但还是没有，所以我认为我们
pretty much going to have to wrap to
几乎必须包装
almost 30 minutes after the webinar was
网络研讨会结束后将近30分钟
supposed to be over which is awesome so
应该在那很棒
deeply appreciate your questions this is
非常感谢您的问题，这是
great and these are not like these are
很棒，这些不像这些
these are really great questions so
这些真的是很好的问题，所以
thanks it's clear that you y'all really
谢谢，很明显，你们真的
engaged in this and they're really
从事这个，他们真的
actively thinking about I think that's
积极思考我认为那是
awesome we'd love to help you more on
太棒了，我们很乐意为您提供更多帮助
you know if you go to the few of the
你知道如果你去几个
webpage that Matt's got up there on this
马特在上面的网页
on the browser or just Google for
在浏览器或Google上
pivotal cloud platform Roadshow we're
关键的云平台路演我们
doing a united states-based tour
进行美国巡回演出
actually excuse me it's not just United
不好意思我不只是曼联
States it is International on yeah I
国家，是的，我是国际的
think it's Munich and there's a few
以为是慕尼黑，有几个
others but there's a oh thank you
其他人，但是有一个哦，谢谢
perfect yeah
太好了
man yep on so you can see some of the
是的，所以您可以看到一些
upcoming cities and you know the event
即将到来的城市，你知道这个事件
really does kind of focus and talk quite
真的很专注和说话
a bit about micro service architecture
关于微服务架构
how that relates to platforms of service
与服务平台的关系如何
how that relates to you know some of the
与您的关系如何
spring cloud technologies and DevOps and
Spring Cloud技术和DevOps以及
you know etc etc a lot of things we
你知道等等我们有很多事情
Matt's touched on today so I highly
马特今天感动了我
encourage you to tell your friends about
鼓励您告诉朋友
these events tell your co-workers about
这些事件告诉您的同事
these events and register for them if
这些事件，并为他们注册
they're in a city that's convenient to
他们在一个方便的城市
you on free and we're going to continue
您免费，我们将继续
to be running these I think the word I
运行这些，我想我这个词
think the word from I think the word
从我想到这个词
from from management is that we are
来自管理层的是
going to continue to be running these
将继续运行这些
things so even if you miss this time
所以即使你错过了这次
around I think we're going to be doing
周围，​​我认为我们将要做
this cloud this Roadshow again so keep
这次路演又阴云密布，继续
keep an eye you know keep an eye on this
留心你知道的
on this page and you know keep keep
在此页面上，您知道保持
looking for more events and obviously
寻找更多的活动，显然
you know if you want to subscribe to at
您知道是否要订阅
Cloud Foundry on Twitter at Spring
Spring 在Twitter上的Cloud Foundry
Central on spring on Twitter you know
中央在推特上的 Spring 你知道
you'll hear about these from from us as
您将从我们这里听到有关这些信息的信息
well but um okay great so I'm just going
很好，但是很好，所以我就去
to wrap up a little bit and just mention
总结一下，只提一下
to everybody you know we are recording
给认识的每个人
this talk and it's going to be posted on
这个演讲，它将被发布在
spring Daioh /video sometime in the next
Spring 大王/视频在未来的某个时候
two weeks on if you want to get a
如果你想得到一个两周
notification of the webinar replay being
网络研讨会重播的通知
available so you can share it with your
可用，因此您可以与自己分享
co-workers and such um you know just
同事，这样的你知道
subscribe to the atom feed it's bring a
订阅原子饲料，它带来了
blog and you'll also get all the great
博客，您还将获得所有的好处
blog content from our engineering teams
工程团队的博客内容
or you can you know if you just want the
或者您可以知道是否只想要
videos you know for some reason or you
您出于某种原因知道的视频或您
know you can subscribe to the YouTube
知道您可以订阅YouTube
channel
渠道
what's your at Spring il video redirects
您在Spring il的视频重定向功能是什么
you to UM also on November 4th excuse me
您也将于11月4日去UM，对不起
sorry on October 23rd apologize later
对不起，10月23日晚些时候道歉
this week just this Thursday Josh long
这个星期正好是这个星期四
is coming back with the Vaadin team
与Vaadin团队一起回来
which is a GWT based UI framework and
这是一个基于GWT的UI框架，
they're going to be talking about
他们将要谈论
building bootiful haha you eyes with
建立你眼中的战利品哈哈
spring boots and Vaadin again this is a
spring boot 和Vaadin再次这是一个
free event you can register for that if
免费活动可以注册，如果
you go to our blog or go to any of the
您可以访问我们的博客或访问任何
latest this week in spring entries from
Spring 最新消息，来自
josh you'll you'll find links to the
乔希，你会发现链接到
registration page and to continue our my
注册页面并继续我们的我的
her service webinar series on Tuesday
她在星期二的服务网络研讨会系列
November 4th of the good doctor Dave
好医生戴夫11月4日
sire will be coming to talk to us about
父亲会来和我们谈谈
security for micro services with spring
Spring微服务的安全性
and oh uh - didn't see any security
哦-没有看到任何安全提示
questions from you guys today but um you
今天你们的问题，但是你呢
know certainly something that certainly
当然知道某些东西
something that you know we're going to
你知道我们要去做的事
want to look at it you get out of sort
想要看它，您会不满意
of exploration phase and into you know
探索阶段，进入您所知道的
testing and eventually production um so
测试并最终生产um so
that's on Tuesday November 4th um and
那是11月4日星期二，
yeah I think lastly if you're interested
是的，我想如果你有兴趣的话
in spring cloud just realize that we
在 Spring 的云中，才意识到我们
have not enable direct HTTP downloads on
尚未在上启用直接HTTP下载
our site for the spring binary so
我们的 Spring 二进制网站
typically we want people to get them
通常我们希望人们得到他们
from maven and Gradle because it's just
来自Maven和Gradle，因为它只是
a much better experience if you're
如果您是一个更好的体验
really desperate and you need HDTV
真的很绝望，你需要高清电视
download you can get them from our
下载您可以从我们的网站上获取它们
artifactory server on repo spring dot IO
回购spring dot IO上的工件服务器
again this repo dot spring that IO and
再次，这个回购点反弹了IO和
if you google for the spring the top
如果您用谷歌搜索 Spring
repository fact it'll it'll show you how
它会告诉你如何
to you know how to deal with that um
你知道如何处理那个嗯
great and most importantly please you
太好了，最重要的是请你
know we're going full-bore on spring
知道我们 Spring 会满口
cloud and micro services and obviously
云和微服务，显然
Cloud Foundry is a you know the Cloud
Cloud Foundry是您知道的Cloud
Foundry team is definitely on fire so
铸造团队肯定着火了
give us your feedback on Twitter at
在以下位置给我们您对Twitter的反馈
Cloud Foundry and at Spring Central and
Cloud Foundry和Spring Central和
just thank you so much for all the great
真的非常感谢你
questions and joining us today um I
问题和今天加入我们
think we pretty much got everyone's got
认为我们几乎得到了所有人的认可
everyone's got everyone's questions so I
每个人都有每个人的问题，所以我
look forward to seeing on a webinar
期待在网络研讨会上看到
again real soon we'll be doing this to
再次真实，我们将这样做
get a 10:00 a.m. if you want to try to
如果您想尝试上午10:00
we didn't get your question answered and
我们没有回答您的问题，
you want to sneak back in um I'll
你想偷偷溜回来，我会
remember your name uh man anything you
记住你的名字
want to say to wrap up I think you
想说总结我想你
covered it pretty well I'm just excited
覆盖得很好我很兴奋
to have as many people around for this
为此有尽可能多的人
long two to talk architecture question
长两人谈建筑问题
so thanks guys for uh for hanging out
所以谢谢大家一起出去玩
with you with me and I really hope it
和你在一起，我真的很希望
was super valuable to you cool man it
对你来说很有价值
was great I definitely learned something
太好了，我肯定学到了一些东西
what listen to this too and you know you
什么也听这个，你知道你
know I spend a lot of time on this stuff
知道我在这个东西上花了很多时间
so thank you alright folks see you again
好，谢谢大家再见
soon take care
快点照顾
Thanks
谢谢
you
您